<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ancient Astronauts on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/topics/ancient-astronauts/</link><description>Recent content in Ancient Astronauts on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/topics/ancient-astronauts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Gentleman’s Joyous Esotericism: Jean Sendy Above and Beyond the Ancient Aliens</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/a-gentlemans-joyous-esotericism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/a-gentlemans-joyous-esotericism/</guid><description>In his paper &amp;ldquo;A Gentleman’s Joyous Esotericism: Jean Sendy Above and Beyond the Ancient Aliens,&amp;rdquo; Stefano Bigliardi discusses the work of Jean Sendy, a French esoteric writer who explored the idea of ancient astronauts and extraterrestrial intervention in human history. Bigliardi provides an overview of Sendy&amp;rsquo;s life and work, including his theories on the origins of humanity, the influence of extraterrestrial beings, and the possible connections between various mythologies and ancient cultures.</description></item><item><title>Echoes of Eden: What secrets of human potential were buried with our ancestors' memories of ET contact?</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/echoes-of-eden/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/echoes-of-eden/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Echoes of Eden&amp;rdquo; by Paul Anthony Wallis delves into the potential connections between human history and extraterrestrial contacts as depicted in ancient narratives worldwide. The book explores the idea that entities described in these stories, which we would today classify as extraterrestrial beings (ETs), have played a significant role in human history. Wallis takes the reader on a global journey, from Senate briefings in Washington DC to secret ceremonies in southern Africa, and from strange phenomena in Australia and Iraq to mysterious encounters in modern Brazil and ancient Greece.</description></item><item><title>Escaping from Eden: Does Genesis teach that the human race was created by God or engineered by ETs?</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/escaping-from-eden/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/escaping-from-eden/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Escaping from Eden&amp;rdquo; by Paul Wallis is a book that reexamines the stories of the Book of Genesis. Wallis suggests that anomalies in the text indicate we are not reading the original versions of these stories. He explores what the original narratives might have been, particularly regarding human origins, which he believes were almost obliterated from the Hebrew Scriptures in the 6th century BC and suppressed in Christian writings in the 2nd and 3rd centuries AD.</description></item><item><title>Extraterrestrials Took Me To Their Planet</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/extraterrestrials-took-me-to-their-planet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/extraterrestrials-took-me-to-their-planet/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Extraterrestrials Took Me to Their Planet&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Claude Vorilhon, also known as Raël, the founder of the Raëlian Movement. The book is a sequel to Raël&amp;rsquo;s first book, &amp;ldquo;The Book Which Tells the Truth,&amp;rdquo; and it expands on the ideas and teachings presented in that work. In &amp;ldquo;Extraterrestrials Took Me to Their Planet,&amp;rdquo; Raël describes his experiences with extraterrestrial beings, whom he refers to as the Elohim.</description></item><item><title>Hard to Be a God</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/hard-to-be-a-god/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/hard-to-be-a-god/</guid><description>Hard to Be a God (1989) is a West German-Soviet-French-Swiss science fiction film directed by Peter Fleischmann, based on the novel of the same name by Arkady and Boris Strugatsky. The film is set on a distant planet that mirrors Earth&amp;rsquo;s Middle Ages, where society has not progressed beyond a primitive, feudal state. This alien world is being observed by Earth scientists posing as noble feudal lords.
The central character, Anton, is one of the scientists sent from Earth.</description></item><item><title>Let's Welcome The Extraterrestrials</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/lets-welcome-the-extraterrestrials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/lets-welcome-the-extraterrestrials/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s Welcome the Extraterrestrials,&amp;rdquo; the third book in the Raelian series, is a compilation of Rael&amp;rsquo;s responses to frequently asked questions post-publication of his first two books. It addresses apparent contradictions between his earlier messages, clarifies the Raelian stance on various topics, and offers insights into the beliefs and teachings of the Raelian Movement. The book delves into the origins of life on Earth, the role of the Elohim in human history, the relationship between humans and their creators, and the future of humanity in relation to extraterrestrial life.</description></item><item><title>Raelian Movement | The true origin of life on Earth: Extraterrestrials created us in their image</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/rael-dot-org/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/rael-dot-org/</guid><description>The Raelian Movement, founded in 1974, centers on the teachings of Rael, who claims to have encountered the Elohim, a group of scientists purported to have created humanity. The movement has grown to over 130,000 members across more than 120 countries. It focuses on spreading the Elohim&amp;rsquo;s message and building an embassy for them on Earth, as detailed in Rael&amp;rsquo;s teachings. This non-profit organization is funded by its members, emphasizing a vision of a world where science is paramount and violence is eradicated.</description></item><item><title>Space a Go Go (archived website)</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/space-a-gogo-dot-com/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/space-a-gogo-dot-com/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Space a Go Go&amp;rdquo; is a website that presents the theory that humans were created by extraterrestrials, drawing on archaeological evidence and interpretations of ancient texts. It suggests that UFOs are piloted by extraterrestrials who have been trying to make their existence known to humanity. The site references the work of Zecharia Sitchin, who claimed that ancient clay tablets from Iraq recorded the creation of humans by extraterrestrials. It also mentions geneticists questioning the natural evolution theory, suggesting that human genetic code indicates an extraterrestrial author.</description></item><item><title>The Bible Is Not a Sacred Book — The Great Deception</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/the-bible-is-not-a-sacred-book/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/the-bible-is-not-a-sacred-book/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;La Bibbia non è un libro sacro. Il grande inganno&amp;rdquo; (&amp;ldquo;The Bible is Not a Sacred Book. The Great Deception&amp;rdquo;) by Mauro Biglino presents a controversial view of the Bible, particularly the Old Testament. Biglino argues that the Bible does not contain a spiritually understood divinity and that there is no worship directed towards God in it. He questions the traditional understanding of the Bible, raising issues like the multiple versions of the Bible, the unknown authors and time of its writing, the real nature of the Tree of Life, and the idea that humans are genetically modified organisms (GMOs).</description></item><item><title>The Coming Of The Gods</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/the-coming-of-the-gods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/the-coming-of-the-gods/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The Coming of the Gods&amp;rdquo; by Jean Sendy explores the concept that advanced extraterrestrial civilizations, referred to as &amp;ldquo;gods,&amp;rdquo; have been visiting Earth for thousands of years, significantly influencing human history and religious beliefs. Sendy attributes many technological and cultural advancements, the creation of religious beliefs, and the inspiration for ancient myths and legends to these extraterrestrial beings. He suggests that these interactions between humans and these &amp;ldquo;gods&amp;rdquo; have occurred in various forms, including direct communication and the performance of miracles.</description></item></channel></rss>