<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Genesis on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/topics/genesis/</link><description>Recent content in Genesis on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/topics/genesis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Echoes of Eden: What secrets of human potential were buried with our ancestors' memories of ET contact?</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/echoes-of-eden/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/echoes-of-eden/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Echoes of Eden&amp;rdquo; by Paul Anthony Wallis delves into the potential connections between human history and extraterrestrial contacts as depicted in ancient narratives worldwide. The book explores the idea that entities described in these stories, which we would today classify as extraterrestrial beings (ETs), have played a significant role in human history. Wallis takes the reader on a global journey, from Senate briefings in Washington DC to secret ceremonies in southern Africa, and from strange phenomena in Australia and Iraq to mysterious encounters in modern Brazil and ancient Greece.</description></item><item><title>Escaping from Eden: Does Genesis teach that the human race was created by God or engineered by ETs?</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/escaping-from-eden/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/escaping-from-eden/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Escaping from Eden&amp;rdquo; by Paul Wallis is a book that reexamines the stories of the Book of Genesis. Wallis suggests that anomalies in the text indicate we are not reading the original versions of these stories. He explores what the original narratives might have been, particularly regarding human origins, which he believes were almost obliterated from the Hebrew Scriptures in the 6th century BC and suppressed in Christian writings in the 2nd and 3rd centuries AD.</description></item><item><title>Is Genesis History?</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/is-genesis-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/is-genesis-history/</guid><description>Is Genesis History?&amp;quot; is a 2017 American film directed by Thomas Purifoy Jr., which presents the perspective of Young Earth creationism. This form of creation science challenges established scientific facts regarding the origins of the universe, Earth, solar system, and life itself, advocating for a literal interpretation of the biblical narratives. The film posits that the Earth was created in six 24-hour days and supports the Genesis accounts of Adam and Eve, the fall, a global flood, and the Tower of Babel.</description></item><item><title>Science After Babel</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/science-after-babel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/science-after-babel/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Science After Babel&amp;rdquo; by David Berlinski is a book that challenges the established norms and widely accepted theories in contemporary science. Berlinski, known for his deep learning, close reasoning, and sharp wit, critiques what he considers to be the shibboleths of modern science. These include widely accepted concepts in Darwinism, reductionism, the Standard Model of particle physics, and the idea of &amp;ldquo;talking&amp;rdquo; chimpanzees.
In his book, Berlinski questions the solidity of what is often passed off as secure scientific knowledge.</description></item><item><title>Sefaria: A Living Library of Torah</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/sefaria/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/sefaria/</guid><description>Sefaria, founded in 2011 by journalist Joshua Foer and Brett Lockspeiser, a former product manager at Google, is a remarkable digital library of Jewish texts. Its name, derived from the Hebrew words &amp;ldquo;sefer&amp;rdquo; (book) and &amp;ldquo;sifria&amp;rdquo; (library), encapsulates its mission to be a comprehensive, accessible repository of Jewish knowledge​​​​.
The platform is designed as an open-source, free-content digital library, offering a wide array of Jewish texts in original languages like Hebrew, Aramaic, and Judeo-Arabic, along with translations.</description></item><item><title>The Devil's Delusion: Atheism and Its Scientific Pretension</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/the-devils-delusion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/the-devils-delusion/</guid><description>In &amp;ldquo;The Devil&amp;rsquo;s Delusion: Atheism and Its Scientific Pretensions,&amp;rdquo; David Berlinski mounts a vigorous critique of scientific atheism, particularly addressing the assertions made by figures like Richard Dawkins and Sam Harris. Berlinski, a secular Jew and mathematician, questions the completeness and authority of science in answering profound existential and moral questions.
Berlinski argues that the science often cited by atheists to debunk religious beliefs actually does not conclusively negate the possibility of a divine existence.</description></item><item><title>The Scars of Eden: Has humanity confused the idea of God with memories of ET contact?</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/the-scars-of-eden/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/the-scars-of-eden/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The Scars of Eden&amp;rdquo; by Paul Wallis, following his previous work &amp;ldquo;Escaping from Eden,&amp;rdquo; explores whether the world&amp;rsquo;s mythologies, including the Bible, are actual accounts of God or ancestral memories of extraterrestrial contact. Wallis delves into ancient stories of contact, adaptation, and abduction, relating them to contemporary experiences worldwide. He includes insights from ancestral voices, modern experiencers, and renowned researchers, discussing recent disclosures from the US Navy, the Pentagon, and French Intelligence.</description></item><item><title>The Sky People</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/the-sky-people/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/the-sky-people/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The Sky People&amp;rdquo; by Brinsley Le Poer Trench offers a unique interpretation of human history and extraterrestrial involvement. Trench, in his book, argues that significant Biblical figures, including Adam and Eve and Noah, were originally residents of Mars. He bases this theory on what he perceives as inconsistencies between the Biblical description of the Garden of Eden and earthly environments, suggesting that the Garden of Eden was actually located on Mars, supported by his mention of canals on Mars.</description></item></channel></rss>