<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>At a glance on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/intro/at-a-glance/</link><description>Recent content in At a glance on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/intro/at-a-glance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Wheel of Heaven 🌌</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/intro/wheel-of-heaven/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/intro/wheel-of-heaven/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve just stumbled upon the Introduction section of this website, you might be wondering what exactly Wheel of Heaven is all about. At its core, Wheel of Heaven is a web-based knowledge repository that explores the hypothesis that life on Earth was intelligently designed by an extraterrestrial civilization with the capability of interstellar travel.
In simple terms, this site suggests that the origins of sentient life on Earth cannot be solely attributed to chance or the chaos of nature, but instead have a deliberate purpose that is encoded in ancient scriptures and artifacts, as well as being preserved in religious traditions.</description></item><item><title>The Setting</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/intro/the-setting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/intro/the-setting/</guid><description>If you have made it this far, it is clear that you are seeking to understand the reason for the existence of this website. We are thrilled to embark on this thought-provoking journey with you, one that may be life-altering or at the very least, provide a newfound appreciation for expanding your mind. Get ready for an adventure that takes us from the foundations of civilization, through the beginning of history and up to present day, focusing on the most crucial events that have shaped our world.</description></item><item><title>The Foundation</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/intro/the-foundation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/intro/the-foundation/</guid><description>Considering the hypothesis outlined in the previous chapter, it becomes evident that a framework of thought emerges that enables us to create a consistent portrayal of the possible origins of life on Earth. The aesthetics provided by this portrayal form the foundation of the grand narrative we put forward. This narrative depicts how sentient life on planet Earth is best explained as being another link in an interstellar chain of planetary civilizations.</description></item><item><title>The Hypothesis</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/intro/the-hypothesis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/intro/the-hypothesis/</guid><description>The hypothesis presented here at Wheel of Heaven is profoundly influenced by the Raëlian revelations, as it embraces the core message of the Elohim&amp;rsquo;s role in creating life on Earth. By considering the Raëlian messages to be authentic, Wheel of Heaven proposes a more nuanced understanding of the Raëlian messages and their implications within the context of our rapidly evolving world.
In the canon of the Raëlian messages, the Elohim are portrayed as an advanced extraterrestrial civilization responsible for creating life on Earth.</description></item></channel></rss>