<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Religion on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/topics/religion/</link><description>Recent content in Religion on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/topics/religion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Gentleman’s Joyous Esotericism: Jean Sendy Above and Beyond the Ancient Aliens</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/a-gentlemans-joyous-esotericism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/a-gentlemans-joyous-esotericism/</guid><description>In his paper &amp;ldquo;A Gentleman’s Joyous Esotericism: Jean Sendy Above and Beyond the Ancient Aliens,&amp;rdquo; Stefano Bigliardi discusses the work of Jean Sendy, a French esoteric writer who explored the idea of ancient astronauts and extraterrestrial intervention in human history. Bigliardi provides an overview of Sendy&amp;rsquo;s life and work, including his theories on the origins of humanity, the influence of extraterrestrial beings, and the possible connections between various mythologies and ancient cultures.</description></item><item><title>Extraterrestrials Took Me To Their Planet</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/extraterrestrials-took-me-to-their-planet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/extraterrestrials-took-me-to-their-planet/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Extraterrestrials Took Me to Their Planet&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Claude Vorilhon, also known as Raël, the founder of the Raëlian Movement. The book is a sequel to Raël&amp;rsquo;s first book, &amp;ldquo;The Book Which Tells the Truth,&amp;rdquo; and it expands on the ideas and teachings presented in that work. In &amp;ldquo;Extraterrestrials Took Me to Their Planet,&amp;rdquo; Raël describes his experiences with extraterrestrial beings, whom he refers to as the Elohim.</description></item><item><title>Internet Sacred Text Archive</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/internet-sacred-text-archive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/internet-sacred-text-archive/</guid><description>The Internet Sacred Text Archive (ISTA), founded by John Bruno Hare in 1999 in Santa Cruz, California, is a website dedicated to preserving electronic public domain religious texts. Hare, a software engineer, initiated this project from his home as an intellectual challenge, digitizing over 1,000 public domain books on religion, folklore, and mythology to promote religious tolerance through knowledge. The archive&amp;rsquo;s texts are divided into 77 categories, and its maintenance costs are supported by sales of the website&amp;rsquo;s content on DVDs, CDs, or USB flash drives.</description></item><item><title>Is Genesis History?</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/is-genesis-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/is-genesis-history/</guid><description>Is Genesis History?&amp;quot; is a 2017 American film directed by Thomas Purifoy Jr., which presents the perspective of Young Earth creationism. This form of creation science challenges established scientific facts regarding the origins of the universe, Earth, solar system, and life itself, advocating for a literal interpretation of the biblical narratives. The film posits that the Earth was created in six 24-hour days and supports the Genesis accounts of Adam and Eve, the fall, a global flood, and the Tower of Babel.</description></item><item><title>Let's Welcome The Extraterrestrials</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/lets-welcome-the-extraterrestrials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/lets-welcome-the-extraterrestrials/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s Welcome the Extraterrestrials,&amp;rdquo; the third book in the Raelian series, is a compilation of Rael&amp;rsquo;s responses to frequently asked questions post-publication of his first two books. It addresses apparent contradictions between his earlier messages, clarifies the Raelian stance on various topics, and offers insights into the beliefs and teachings of the Raelian Movement. The book delves into the origins of life on Earth, the role of the Elohim in human history, the relationship between humans and their creators, and the future of humanity in relation to extraterrestrial life.</description></item><item><title>Sefaria: A Living Library of Torah</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/sefaria/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/sefaria/</guid><description>Sefaria, founded in 2011 by journalist Joshua Foer and Brett Lockspeiser, a former product manager at Google, is a remarkable digital library of Jewish texts. Its name, derived from the Hebrew words &amp;ldquo;sefer&amp;rdquo; (book) and &amp;ldquo;sifria&amp;rdquo; (library), encapsulates its mission to be a comprehensive, accessible repository of Jewish knowledge​​​​.
The platform is designed as an open-source, free-content digital library, offering a wide array of Jewish texts in original languages like Hebrew, Aramaic, and Judeo-Arabic, along with translations.</description></item><item><title>Tanakh</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/tanakh/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/tanakh/</guid><description>The Tanakh, also known as the Hebrew Bible, is the canonical collection of Jewish texts, which is also a significant part of Christian scriptures. It is divided into three sections: the Torah (Teaching or Law), the Nevi&amp;rsquo;im (Prophets), and the Ketuvim (Writings). The word &amp;ldquo;Tanakh&amp;rdquo; is an acronym derived from these three divisions.
The Torah (Law or Teaching): Also known as the Pentateuch, the Torah comprises the first five books of the Bible - Genesis, Exodus, Leviticus, Numbers, and Deuteronomy.</description></item><item><title>The Church of Jesus of Latter-Day Saints: Scriptures</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/the-church-of-jesus-latter-day-saints-scriptures/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/the-church-of-jesus-latter-day-saints-scriptures/</guid><description>The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints&amp;rsquo; Scriptures resource offers a comprehensive collection of religious texts central to the faith, including the Old Testament, New Testament, Book of Mormon, Doctrine and Covenants, Pearl of Great Price, and various study aids and proclamations. The history of these scriptures reveals a dynamic process of compilation, revision, and enhancement to make these sacred texts accessible and relevant to its members.
Key milestones in the history of these scriptures include the commissioning of the King James Version of the Bible by King James I, the translation and subsequent revisions of the Book of Mormon initiated by Joseph Smith, and the compilation of Joseph Smith&amp;rsquo;s revelations into the Book of Commandments, which later evolved into the Doctrine and Covenants​.</description></item><item><title>Wonders in the Sky: Unexplained Aerial Objects from Antiquity to Modern Times</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/wonders-in-the-sky/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/wonders-in-the-sky/</guid><description>Wonders in the Sky: Unexplained Aerial Objects from Antiquity to Modern Times&amp;quot; by Jacques Vallée and Chris Aubeck is a comprehensive investigation into the history of unidentified flying objects (UFOs). The book examines over 500 reports of UFO sightings from ancient times up to the year 1879, a period before the profound changes brought by the Industrial Revolution and the advent of modern aircraft like airplanes and dirigibles.
The work is noted for its rigorous approach to paranormal investigation, presenting a detailed compendium of pre-twentieth-century UFO accounts.</description></item></channel></rss>