<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pyramids on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/topics/pyramids/</link><description>Recent content in Pyramids on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/topics/pyramids/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ancient Apocalypse</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/ancient-apocalypse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/ancient-apocalypse/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Ancient Apocalypse,&amp;rdquo; a 2022 Netflix documentary series hosted by British writer Graham Hancock, presents a series of pseudoarchaeological theories about an advanced civilization that existed during the last ice age. The series, produced by ITN Productions and highly watched upon release, suggests that this civilization was destroyed in a cataclysm and its survivors introduced agriculture, monumental architecture, and astronomy to hunter-gatherers around the world. Hancock contends that various ancient monuments are evidence of this civilization and accuses archaeologists of ignoring or covering up this alleged evidence.</description></item><item><title>Creators: The Past</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/creators-the-past/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/creators-the-past/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Creators: The Past&amp;rdquo; is an Italian science fiction fantasy film directed by Piergiuseppe Zaia, who also co-wrote the screenplay with Eleonora Fani and composed the soundtrack. The film features a notable cast, including Eleonora Fani, Jennifer Mischiati, Bruce Payne, and guest appearances by Gérard Depardieu and William Shatner. The plot revolves around the manipulation of mankind&amp;rsquo;s destiny by a race of powerful extraterrestrials known as the Creators. It was announced as the first part of a planned trilogy, with the next two installments being &amp;ldquo;Creators: The Present&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Creators: The Future.</description></item><item><title>Fingerprints of the Gods: The Evidence of Earth's Lost Civilization</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/fingerprints-of-the-gods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/fingerprints-of-the-gods/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Fingerprints of the Gods: The Evidence of Earth&amp;rsquo;s Lost Civilization&amp;rdquo; by Graham Hancock, published in 1995, explores the hypothesis of a highly advanced civilization existing in prehistory, serving as the progenitor of all known ancient civilizations. Hancock proposes that this civilization, centered around Antarctica, ended catastrophically at the end of the last ice age but passed on significant knowledge in astronomy, architecture, and mathematics. The evidence for this lost civilization, according to Hancock, is found in ancient Egypt and American civilizations like the Olmec, Aztec, and Maya.</description></item><item><title>Space a Go Go (archived website)</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/space-a-gogo-dot-com/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/space-a-gogo-dot-com/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Space a Go Go&amp;rdquo; is a website that presents the theory that humans were created by extraterrestrials, drawing on archaeological evidence and interpretations of ancient texts. It suggests that UFOs are piloted by extraterrestrials who have been trying to make their existence known to humanity. The site references the work of Zecharia Sitchin, who claimed that ancient clay tablets from Iraq recorded the creation of humans by extraterrestrials. It also mentions geneticists questioning the natural evolution theory, suggesting that human genetic code indicates an extraterrestrial author.</description></item><item><title>The Revelation of the Pyramids</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/the-revelation-of-the-pyramid/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/the-revelation-of-the-pyramid/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The Revelation of the Pyramids,&amp;rdquo; a French documentary directed by Patrice Pooyard and released in 2010, delves into pseudo-historical theories proposed by Jacques Grimault. Grimault&amp;rsquo;s unpublished works suggest a slow cycle of geological changes on Earth, including shifts in magnetic poles, causing catastrophic events every 26,000 years. He theorizes that an ancient civilization, predating ours, was destroyed by these catastrophes, and that they built the Pyramids of Giza and other ancient structures.</description></item></channel></rss>