<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Futurism on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/topics/futurism/</link><description>Recent content in Futurism on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/topics/futurism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cyberparadism Manifesto</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/cyberparadism-manifesto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/cyberparadism-manifesto/</guid><description>The Cyberparadism Manifesto, found on GitHub, outlines a vision for a future shaped by the positive potential of technology and scientific progress. At its core, Cyberparadism focuses on using technology to enhance the human experience, promote sustainability, and foster a collective sense of purpose and responsibility. It is not a political or economic manifesto, but rather an aesthetic declaration that seeks to inspire and stimulate imagination. The manifesto embraces the idea that technology can create a world of abundance, equity, and harmony with nature.</description></item><item><title>Jurassic World</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/jurassic-world/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/jurassic-world/</guid><description>Jurassic World is a 2015 American science fiction adventure film and the fourth installment in the Jurassic Park franchise. Directed by Colin Trevorrow and written by Trevorrow, Derek Connolly, Rick Jaffa, and Amanda Silver, the film is set 22 years after the events of the original Jurassic Park and takes place on the same fictional Central American island of Isla Nublar, off Costa Rica&amp;rsquo;s Pacific Coast.
In Jurassic World, the island has been transformed into a fully functioning dinosaur theme park, as originally envisioned by John Hammond.</description></item><item><title>The Techno-Optimist Manifesto</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/the-techno-optimist-manifesto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/resources/the-techno-optimist-manifesto/</guid><description>The Techno-Optimist Manifesto presents a vision of a future where technology is the driving force behind societal progress and human well-being. It challenges the pervasive narrative that technology causes harm, such as job loss, environmental degradation, and societal ills, arguing instead that technology has been, and should continue to be, a source of human advancement and achievement.
Central to the manifesto is the belief that societies, like sharks, must continue to grow or face decline.</description></item></channel></rss>