<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Tradition on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/topics/the-tradition/</link><description>Recent content in The Tradition on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/topics/the-tradition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ancient Apocalypse</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/ancient-apocalypse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/ancient-apocalypse/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Ancient Apocalypse,&amp;rdquo; a 2022 Netflix documentary series hosted by British writer Graham Hancock, presents a series of pseudoarchaeological theories about an advanced civilization that existed during the last ice age. The series, produced by ITN Productions and highly watched upon release, suggests that this civilization was destroyed in a cataclysm and its survivors introduced agriculture, monumental architecture, and astronomy to hunter-gatherers around the world. Hancock contends that various ancient monuments are evidence of this civilization and accuses archaeologists of ignoring or covering up this alleged evidence.</description></item><item><title>Avesta</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-enoch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-enoch/</guid><description>The Avesta is the holy scripture of Zoroastrianism, one of the world&amp;rsquo;s oldest monotheistic religions. Composed over several centuries, its authorship is traditionally attributed to the prophet Zoroaster (from the Greek transcription Ζωροάστρης, Zōroastrēs), also known as Zarathustra (from the Avestan 𐬰𐬀𐬭𐬀𐬚𐬎𐬱𐬙𐬭𐬀, transliterated Zaraθuštra) but it likely includes contributions from many authors. The Avesta consists of various parts, including hymns, liturgical texts, mythological lore, moral guidance, and prayers. These texts are central to Zoroastrian religious practice and philosophy, emphasizing the cosmic struggle between good and evil.</description></item><item><title>Barton Cylinder</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/barton-cylinder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/barton-cylinder/</guid><description>The Barton Cylinder, also known as CBS 8383, is a significant artifact of Sumerian literature and mythology. Dating from the mid to late 3rd millennium BCE, approximately around 2400 BCE, it is a clay cylinder inscribed with a Sumerian cuneiform text. The cylinder was discovered in 1889 at the site of Nippur during excavations by the University of Pennsylvania and is currently housed in the University of Pennsylvania Museum of Archaeology and Anthropology.</description></item><item><title>Book of Abraham</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-abraham/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-abraham/</guid><description>The Book of Abraham is a work that is considered scripture by the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints (LDS Church). It is believed to be an inspired translation of writings attributed to Abraham. The book was first published in 1842 and later canonized as part of the LDS Church&amp;rsquo;s Pearl of Great Price in 1880.
The content of the Book of Abraham includes a narrative of Abraham&amp;rsquo;s life, his travels to Canaan and Egypt, and visions he received concerning the universe, a pre-mortal existence, and the creation of the world.</description></item><item><title>Book of Enoch</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/avesta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/avesta/</guid><description>The Book of Enoch, also known as 1 Enoch, is an ancient Hebrew apocalyptic religious text traditionally attributed to the patriarch Enoch. It contains unique material on the origins of demons and Nephilim, the reasons why some angels fell from heaven, and a prophetic exposition of the thousand-year reign of the Messiah. The oldest sections are estimated to date from 300–200 BC, with the latest part around 100 BC. The text, thought to be originally written in Aramaic or Hebrew, is found in various fragments, including the Dead Sea Scrolls.</description></item><item><title>Book of Mormon</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-mormon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-mormon/</guid><description>The Book of Mormon, foundational to the Latter Day Saint movement, is a religious text published by Joseph Smith in 1830. Smith described it as a translation of golden plates shown to him by an angel, Moroni. The narrative details the history of ancient peoples in the Americas, focusing on their spiritual journey and teachings, with a pivotal event being the appearance of Jesus Christ post-resurrection. It&amp;rsquo;s considered by adherents as a complementary scripture to the Bible, offering insights into Christian theology and moral teachings.</description></item><item><title>Creators: The Past</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/creators-the-past/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/creators-the-past/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Creators: The Past&amp;rdquo; is an Italian science fiction fantasy film directed by Piergiuseppe Zaia, who also co-wrote the screenplay with Eleonora Fani and composed the soundtrack. The film features a notable cast, including Eleonora Fani, Jennifer Mischiati, Bruce Payne, and guest appearances by Gérard Depardieu and William Shatner. The plot revolves around the manipulation of mankind&amp;rsquo;s destiny by a race of powerful extraterrestrials known as the Creators. It was announced as the first part of a planned trilogy, with the next two installments being &amp;ldquo;Creators: The Present&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Creators: The Future.</description></item><item><title>Debate between sheep and grain</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/debate-between-sheep-and-grain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/debate-between-sheep-and-grain/</guid><description>The &amp;ldquo;Debate between sheep and grain&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Myth of cattle and grain&amp;rdquo; is a significant Sumerian creation myth from the mid to late 3rd millennium BC. This myth is one of several &amp;ldquo;debate&amp;rdquo; topics known from Sumerian literature, characterized as disputations. Such debates were philosophical in nature and often addressed humanity&amp;rsquo;s place in the world, reflecting a sophisticated level of abstract thought in ancient Mesopotamian societies.
In this particular myth, the god An creates the cattle-goddess Lahar and the grain goddess Ashnan to provide food and clothing for the Anunnaki, the deities who, according to Sumerian belief, created mankind.</description></item><item><title>Debate between Winter and Summer</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/debate-between-winter-and-summer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/debate-between-winter-and-summer/</guid><description>The &amp;ldquo;Debate between Winter and Summer,&amp;rdquo; also known as the &amp;ldquo;Myth of Emesh and Enten,&amp;rdquo; is a Sumerian creation myth dating from the mid to late 3rd millennium BC. This narrative is composed on clay tablets and is part of the ancient Mesopotamian tradition of disputations or debate poems.
In this story, two cultural entities, initially identified as vegetation gods Emesh and Enten by Kramer, represent the natural phenomena of Summer and Winter, respectively.</description></item><item><title>Divine Signposts</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/divine-signposts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/divine-signposts/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Divine Signposts&amp;rdquo; (大本, Ōmoto) by Onisaburo Deguchi (出口王仁三郎) is a foundational text in the spiritual and religious tradition of Ōmoto (大本), a Japanese new religious movement. Written in 1904 when Onisaburo was 33 years old, this work is one of his earliest writings and consists of 14 volumes. It lays out the basis of Ōmoto&amp;rsquo;s teachings, emphasizing the essence of faith and Onisaburo&amp;rsquo;s mission of world salvation.
This sacred text is intended to be read by Ōmoto believers as a part of their daily spiritual practice, serving as both a doctrinal book and a guide to true faith.</description></item></channel></rss>