<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chronologie on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/intro/timeline/</link><description>Recent content in Chronologie on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/intro/timeline/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Préambule</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/intro/pr%C3%A9ambule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/intro/pr%C3%A9ambule/</guid><description>La chronologie commence un peu avant environ –22'000, juste à la porte de l&amp;rsquo;Ère du Capricorne. Ce qui précède l&amp;rsquo;Ère du Capricorne est un Âge du Verseau de la Grande Année précédente. Avant de commencer avec le premier Grand Mois précessionnel, l&amp;rsquo;Âge mondial Capricornien, il vaut la peine d&amp;rsquo;examiner ce qui a conduit à celui-ci. Pour illustrer ce qui s&amp;rsquo;est passé, nous pouvons nous inspirer d&amp;rsquo;un classique de l&amp;rsquo;industrie cinématographique américaine, Jurassic Park.</description></item><item><title>Ère du Capricorne</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/intro/%C3%A8re-du-capricorne/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/intro/%C3%A8re-du-capricorne/</guid><description>Nous commençons par l&amp;rsquo;Ère du Capricorne. L&amp;rsquo;Ère du Capricorne est le premier Mois précessionnel dans le cycle de la Grande Année. Avec la période nominale de 25'920 ans pour l&amp;rsquo;Année de précession, la durée d&amp;rsquo;un Mois de précession est de 2'160 ans. Pendant cette période, le Soleil levant à l&amp;rsquo;équinoxe vernal est aligné avec la constellation du Capricorne dans l&amp;rsquo;écliptique.
Tout comme l&amp;rsquo;année orbitale, définie par la révolution de la Terre autour du Soleil, est divisée en 12 segments mensuels, l&amp;rsquo;Année de précession, également connue sous le nom de Grande Année, est divisée en 12 Mois de précession, ou Grands Mois.</description></item><item><title>Âge du Sagittaire</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/intro/%C3%A2ge-du-sagittaire/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/intro/%C3%A2ge-du-sagittaire/</guid><description>The Age of Sagittarius lasts from –19'650 to –17'490 and follows the Age of Capricorn which lasted up to –19'650.
In the last chapter, The Age of Capricorn, we learned that a group of scientifically inclined spacefaring pioneers managed to find an exoplanet that provided all elements necessary to produce artifical life, including water. The planet they&amp;rsquo;ve found was covered in water and mist, and didn&amp;rsquo;t harbour any life at the moment of its discovery.</description></item><item><title>Âge du Scorpion</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/intro/%C3%A2ge-du-scorpion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/intro/%C3%A2ge-du-scorpion/</guid><description>The Age of Scorpio lasts from –17'490 to –15'330 and follows the Age of Sagittarius which lasted up to –17'490.
In the last chapter, The Age of Sagittarius, we learned that the group of scientifically inclined spacefaring pioneers who managed to find an exoplanet that provided all elements necessary to produce artifical life, including water, studied the planet well enough to capitalize on its capacity to harbour life. The whole planet was covered in water, so they went on to build new outposts on the surface these oceans and kept studying and surveying the constitution of this new planet, especially its ocean and the bottom of it.</description></item><item><title>Âge de la Balance</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/intro/%C3%A2ge-de-la-balance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/intro/%C3%A2ge-de-la-balance/</guid><description>The Age of Libra lasts from –15'330 to –13'170 and follows the Age of Scorpio which lasted up to –15'330.
In the last chapter, The Age of Scorpio, we learned that the group of scientifically inclined spacefaring pioneers who managed to find an exoplanet that provided all elements necessary to produce artifical life, including water, studied the planet well enough to capitalize on its capacity to harbour life. As soon as they managed to terraform a new barren continental land mass out of the bottom of the oceans, they went on to synthetize plant life.</description></item><item><title>Âge de la Vierge</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/intro/%C3%A2ge-de-la-vierge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/intro/%C3%A2ge-de-la-vierge/</guid><description>The Age of Virgo lasts from –13'170 to –11'010 and follows the Age of Libra which lasted up to –13'170.
Fig. 2 - Vernal equinox in 13'170 BC Aquatic and bird kingdoms # Let the waters abound with an abundance of living creatures, and let birds fly above the earth across the face of the firmament of the heavens. Genesis 1: 20.
Next they created the first aquatic animals, from plankton to small fish, then very large fish.</description></item><item><title>Âge du Lion</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/intro/%C3%A2ge-du-lion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/intro/%C3%A2ge-du-lion/</guid><description>The Age of Leo lasts from –11'010 to –8'850 and follows the Age of Virgo which lasted up to –11'010.
Fig. 1 - Vernal equinox in 11010 BC Animal kingdom # Let the earth bring forth the living creature according to its kind: cattle and creeping thing and beast of the earth, each according to its kind. Genesis 1: 24.
After marine organisms and birds, the scientists created land animals on a planet where the vegetation had by now become magnificent.</description></item><item><title>Âge du cancer</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/intro/%C3%A2ge-du-cancer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/intro/%C3%A2ge-du-cancer/</guid><description>Fig. 1 - Vernal equinox in 8850 BC The Age of Cancer lasts from –8'850 to –6'690 and follows the Age of Leo which lasted up to –8'850.
Awakening # The serpent&amp;hellip; said unto the woman&amp;hellip; of the fruit of the tree which is in the midst of the garden&amp;hellip; ye shall not surely die, for Elohim doth know that in the day ye eat thereof, then your eyes shall be opened, and ye shall be like Elohim.</description></item><item><title>Âge des Gémeaux</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/intro/%C3%A2ge-des-g%C3%A9meaux/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/intro/%C3%A2ge-des-g%C3%A9meaux/</guid><description>The Age of Gemini lasts from –6'690 to –4'530 and follows the Age of Cancer which lasted up to –6'690.
From the perspective of Genesis and its seven Days of Creation, the Age of Gemini would represent the Eight Day. The number eight is encoded in the amount of people entering Noah&amp;rsquo;s Ark: Noah and his wife, his three sons and their wives, a total of 8 people.
The Age of Gemini is associated with the eighth day of creation and represents a time of new beginnings and fresh starts.</description></item><item><title>Âge du Taureau</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/intro/%C3%A2ge-du-taureau/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/intro/%C3%A2ge-du-taureau/</guid><description>The Age of Taurus lasts from –4'530 to –2'370 and follows the Age of Gemini which lasted up to –4'530.
Peace in Heaven # The exiled creators were pardoned and allowed to return to their original planet where they pleaded the case of their magnificent creation. As a result, everyone on the distant planet fixed their eyes on the Earth because it was inhabited by people they had themselves created.</description></item></channel></rss>