<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Precession on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/zh/resources/topics/precession/</link><description>Recent content in Precession on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/zh/resources/topics/precession/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Gentleman’s Joyous Esotericism: Jean Sendy Above and Beyond the Ancient Aliens</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/zh/resources/a-gentlemans-joyous-esotericism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/zh/resources/a-gentlemans-joyous-esotericism/</guid><description>In his paper &amp;ldquo;A Gentleman’s Joyous Esotericism: Jean Sendy Above and Beyond the Ancient Aliens,&amp;rdquo; Stefano Bigliardi discusses the work of Jean Sendy, a French esoteric writer who explored the idea of ancient astronauts and extraterrestrial intervention in human history. Bigliardi provides an overview of Sendy&amp;rsquo;s life and work, including his theories on the origins of humanity, the influence of extraterrestrial beings, and the possible connections between various mythologies and ancient cultures.</description></item><item><title>Ancient Apocalypse</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/zh/resources/ancient-apocalypse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/zh/resources/ancient-apocalypse/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Ancient Apocalypse,&amp;rdquo; a 2022 Netflix documentary series hosted by British writer Graham Hancock, presents a series of pseudoarchaeological theories about an advanced civilization that existed during the last ice age. The series, produced by ITN Productions and highly watched upon release, suggests that this civilization was destroyed in a cataclysm and its survivors introduced agriculture, monumental architecture, and astronomy to hunter-gatherers around the world. Hancock contends that various ancient monuments are evidence of this civilization and accuses archaeologists of ignoring or covering up this alleged evidence.</description></item><item><title>Creators: The Past</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/zh/resources/creators-the-past/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/zh/resources/creators-the-past/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Creators: The Past&amp;rdquo; is an Italian science fiction fantasy film directed by Piergiuseppe Zaia, who also co-wrote the screenplay with Eleonora Fani and composed the soundtrack. The film features a notable cast, including Eleonora Fani, Jennifer Mischiati, Bruce Payne, and guest appearances by Gérard Depardieu and William Shatner. The plot revolves around the manipulation of mankind&amp;rsquo;s destiny by a race of powerful extraterrestrials known as the Creators. It was announced as the first part of a planned trilogy, with the next two installments being &amp;ldquo;Creators: The Present&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Creators: The Future.</description></item><item><title>Fingerprints of the Gods: The Evidence of Earth's Lost Civilization</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/zh/resources/fingerprints-of-the-gods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/zh/resources/fingerprints-of-the-gods/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Fingerprints of the Gods: The Evidence of Earth&amp;rsquo;s Lost Civilization&amp;rdquo; by Graham Hancock, published in 1995, explores the hypothesis of a highly advanced civilization existing in prehistory, serving as the progenitor of all known ancient civilizations. Hancock proposes that this civilization, centered around Antarctica, ended catastrophically at the end of the last ice age but passed on significant knowledge in astronomy, architecture, and mathematics. The evidence for this lost civilization, according to Hancock, is found in ancient Egypt and American civilizations like the Olmec, Aztec, and Maya.</description></item><item><title>Hamlet's Mill: An Essay Investigating the Origins of Human Knowledge and Its Transmission Through Myth</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/zh/resources/hamlets-mill/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/zh/resources/hamlets-mill/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Hamlet&amp;rsquo;s Mill: An Essay Investigating the Origins of Human Knowledge and Its Transmission Through Myth,&amp;rdquo; written by Giorgio de Santillana and Hertha von Dechend, presents the argument that ancient mythologies contain sophisticated knowledge of the precession of the equinoxes. This knowledge, they argue, indicates a Neolithic discovery and a long-lived Megalithic civilization of remarkable sophistication, particularly in astronomical observation. The authors suggest that this civilization&amp;rsquo;s knowledge was encoded in myths, often represented by a millstone and a young protagonist, which they interpret primarily through the lens of archaeoastronomy.</description></item><item><title>Kosmographia — The Official Randall Carlson Podcast</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/zh/resources/kosmographia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/zh/resources/kosmographia/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Kosmographia — The Official Randall Carlson Podcast&amp;rdquo; is a thought-provoking and in-depth podcast series hosted by Randall Carlson, a renowned geological and architectural theorist, teacher, and scholar. The podcast delves into a wide array of subjects that intersect science, mythology, geology, and ancient history, reflecting Carlson&amp;rsquo;s multifaceted interests and expertise.
Carlson, known for his meticulous research and comprehensive knowledge, explores theories and evidence related to Earth&amp;rsquo;s geological history, catastrophic events, and the mysteries of ancient civilizations.</description></item><item><title>Mazzaroth | The Alpha and the Omega</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/zh/resources/mazzaroth-dot-com/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/zh/resources/mazzaroth-dot-com/</guid><description>Jim A. Cornwell&amp;rsquo;s website, mazzaroth.com, offers a detailed exploration of the interplay between the zodiac, biblical narratives, and ancient civilizations. It delves into the correlations of zodiac symbols with biblical patriarchs, interprets the creation story in Genesis in relation to astronomical events, and examines the historical and astronomical connections to various periods, such as the Bronze Age and Egyptian Dynasties. The site also explores themes like the New Age, the Antichrist, and biblical prophecies of tribulation, linking these concepts to astronomical interpretations and the concept of completeness symbolized by the number twelve.</description></item><item><title>Mazzaroth; or, The constellations</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/zh/resources/mazzaroth-rolleston/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/zh/resources/mazzaroth-rolleston/</guid><description>Frances Rolleston&amp;rsquo;s book, &amp;ldquo;Mazzaroth; or, The Constellations,&amp;rdquo; explores the significance and symbolism of the constellations in the context of divine revelation and biblical prophecy. She contends that the constellations hold a deeper, spiritual meaning that has been obscured by associations with pagan mythology and a lack of understanding of their original intent.
Rolleston argues that the constellations and their names, which are known worldwide and throughout history, point to a common origin both for humanity and these celestial symbols.</description></item><item><title>The Coming Of The Gods</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/zh/resources/the-coming-of-the-gods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/zh/resources/the-coming-of-the-gods/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The Coming of the Gods&amp;rdquo; by Jean Sendy explores the concept that advanced extraterrestrial civilizations, referred to as &amp;ldquo;gods,&amp;rdquo; have been visiting Earth for thousands of years, significantly influencing human history and religious beliefs. Sendy attributes many technological and cultural advancements, the creation of religious beliefs, and the inspiration for ancient myths and legends to these extraterrestrial beings. He suggests that these interactions between humans and these &amp;ldquo;gods&amp;rdquo; have occurred in various forms, including direct communication and the performance of miracles.</description></item><item><title>The Gospel in the Stars</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/zh/resources/the-gospels-in-the-stars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/zh/resources/the-gospels-in-the-stars/</guid><description>Joseph A. Seiss&amp;rsquo; book &amp;ldquo;The Gospel in the Stars&amp;rdquo; presents a unique interpretation of the constellations, suggesting that they carry a divine message relating to the gospel of Jesus Christ. Seiss, an American pastor and author, proposes that the arrangement and symbolism of the constellations have been used throughout human history as a means to convey knowledge and wisdom, particularly concerning the nature of God and the plan of salvation.</description></item></channel></rss>