<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mythology on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/topics/mythology/</link><description>Recent content in Mythology on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/topics/mythology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Avesta</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-enoch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-enoch/</guid><description>The Avesta is the holy scripture of Zoroastrianism, one of the world&amp;rsquo;s oldest monotheistic religions. Composed over several centuries, its authorship is traditionally attributed to the prophet Zoroaster (from the Greek transcription Ζωροάστρης, Zōroastrēs), also known as Zarathustra (from the Avestan 𐬰𐬀𐬭𐬀𐬚𐬎𐬱𐬙𐬭𐬀, transliterated Zaraθuštra) but it likely includes contributions from many authors. The Avesta consists of various parts, including hymns, liturgical texts, mythological lore, moral guidance, and prayers. These texts are central to Zoroastrian religious practice and philosophy, emphasizing the cosmic struggle between good and evil.</description></item><item><title>Barton Cylinder</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/barton-cylinder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/barton-cylinder/</guid><description>The Barton Cylinder, also known as CBS 8383, is a significant artifact of Sumerian literature and mythology. Dating from the mid to late 3rd millennium BCE, approximately around 2400 BCE, it is a clay cylinder inscribed with a Sumerian cuneiform text. The cylinder was discovered in 1889 at the site of Nippur during excavations by the University of Pennsylvania and is currently housed in the University of Pennsylvania Museum of Archaeology and Anthropology.</description></item><item><title>Book of Enoch</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/avesta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/avesta/</guid><description>The Book of Enoch, also known as 1 Enoch, is an ancient Hebrew apocalyptic religious text traditionally attributed to the patriarch Enoch. It contains unique material on the origins of demons and Nephilim, the reasons why some angels fell from heaven, and a prophetic exposition of the thousand-year reign of the Messiah. The oldest sections are estimated to date from 300–200 BC, with the latest part around 100 BC. The text, thought to be originally written in Aramaic or Hebrew, is found in various fragments, including the Dead Sea Scrolls.</description></item><item><title>Debate between sheep and grain</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/debate-between-sheep-and-grain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/debate-between-sheep-and-grain/</guid><description>The &amp;ldquo;Debate between sheep and grain&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Myth of cattle and grain&amp;rdquo; is a significant Sumerian creation myth from the mid to late 3rd millennium BC. This myth is one of several &amp;ldquo;debate&amp;rdquo; topics known from Sumerian literature, characterized as disputations. Such debates were philosophical in nature and often addressed humanity&amp;rsquo;s place in the world, reflecting a sophisticated level of abstract thought in ancient Mesopotamian societies.
In this particular myth, the god An creates the cattle-goddess Lahar and the grain goddess Ashnan to provide food and clothing for the Anunnaki, the deities who, according to Sumerian belief, created mankind.</description></item><item><title>Debate between Winter and Summer</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/debate-between-winter-and-summer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/debate-between-winter-and-summer/</guid><description>The &amp;ldquo;Debate between Winter and Summer,&amp;rdquo; also known as the &amp;ldquo;Myth of Emesh and Enten,&amp;rdquo; is a Sumerian creation myth dating from the mid to late 3rd millennium BC. This narrative is composed on clay tablets and is part of the ancient Mesopotamian tradition of disputations or debate poems.
In this story, two cultural entities, initially identified as vegetation gods Emesh and Enten by Kramer, represent the natural phenomena of Summer and Winter, respectively.</description></item><item><title>Enlil and Ninlil: The begetting of Nanna</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/enlil-and-ninlil-the-begetting-of-nanna/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/enlil-and-ninlil-the-begetting-of-nanna/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Enlil and Ninlil: The Begetting of Nanna&amp;rdquo; is a Sumerian creation myth that dates back to the mid to late 3rd millennium BC. The story is set in the ancient city of Nippur, which is portrayed as a divine city inhabited by gods before humans. Enlil, a prominent god in the Sumerian pantheon, is featured as a central character in this myth.
The narrative begins with Nun-bar-ce-gunu, a goddess, warning her daughter Ninlil about the potential romantic advances of Enlil.</description></item><item><title>Epic of Gilgamesh</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/epic-of-gilgamesh/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/epic-of-gilgamesh/</guid><description>The Epic of Gilgamesh is an ancient Mesopotamian poem, regarded as one of the earliest great works of literature. It narrates the adventures of Gilgamesh, the historical king of Uruk, and his quest for immortality, exploring themes of friendship, the human condition, and the fear of death. The epic, written in cuneiform on clay tablets, dates back to the early 3rd millennium BCE.
The story begins with the introduction of Gilgamesh, two-thirds god and one-third human, who is a tyrannical king of Uruk.</description></item><item><title>Internet Sacred Text Archive</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/internet-sacred-text-archive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/internet-sacred-text-archive/</guid><description>The Internet Sacred Text Archive (ISTA), founded by John Bruno Hare in 1999 in Santa Cruz, California, is a website dedicated to preserving electronic public domain religious texts. Hare, a software engineer, initiated this project from his home as an intellectual challenge, digitizing over 1,000 public domain books on religion, folklore, and mythology to promote religious tolerance through knowledge. The archive&amp;rsquo;s texts are divided into 77 categories, and its maintenance costs are supported by sales of the website&amp;rsquo;s content on DVDs, CDs, or USB flash drives.</description></item><item><title>Mazzaroth | The Alpha and the Omega</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/mazzaroth-dot-com/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/mazzaroth-dot-com/</guid><description>Jim A. Cornwell&amp;rsquo;s website, mazzaroth.com, offers a detailed exploration of the interplay between the zodiac, biblical narratives, and ancient civilizations. It delves into the correlations of zodiac symbols with biblical patriarchs, interprets the creation story in Genesis in relation to astronomical events, and examines the historical and astronomical connections to various periods, such as the Bronze Age and Egyptian Dynasties. The site also explores themes like the New Age, the Antichrist, and biblical prophecies of tribulation, linking these concepts to astronomical interpretations and the concept of completeness symbolized by the number twelve.</description></item><item><title>Mazzaroth; or, The constellations</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/mazzaroth-rolleston/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/mazzaroth-rolleston/</guid><description>Frances Rolleston&amp;rsquo;s book, &amp;ldquo;Mazzaroth; or, The Constellations,&amp;rdquo; explores the significance and symbolism of the constellations in the context of divine revelation and biblical prophecy. She contends that the constellations hold a deeper, spiritual meaning that has been obscured by associations with pagan mythology and a lack of understanding of their original intent.
Rolleston argues that the constellations and their names, which are known worldwide and throughout history, point to a common origin both for humanity and these celestial symbols.</description></item></channel></rss>