<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>canonical-text on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/medium/canonical-text/</link><description>Recent content in canonical-text on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/medium/canonical-text/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Extraterrestrials Took Me To Their Planet</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/extraterrestrials-took-me-to-their-planet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/extraterrestrials-took-me-to-their-planet/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Extraterrestrials Took Me to Their Planet&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Claude Vorilhon, also known as Raël, the founder of the Raëlian Movement. The book is a sequel to Raël&amp;rsquo;s first book, &amp;ldquo;The Book Which Tells the Truth,&amp;rdquo; and it expands on the ideas and teachings presented in that work. In &amp;ldquo;Extraterrestrials Took Me to Their Planet,&amp;rdquo; Raël describes his experiences with extraterrestrial beings, whom he refers to as the Elohim.</description></item><item><title>Le Livre Qui Dit la Vérité</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/the-book-which-tells-the-truth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/the-book-which-tells-the-truth/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Le Livre Qui Dit la Vérité&amp;rdquo; est un livre écrit par Claude Vorilhon, également connu sous le nom de Raël, le fondateur du Mouvement Raëlien. Le livre détaille les affirmations de Raël concernant ses rencontres avec des êtres extraterrestres et présente ses croyances et enseignements. Selon Raël, les êtres extraterrestres qu&amp;rsquo;il a rencontrés lui ont révélé que la vie sur Terre a été créée par ingénierie génétique par une civilisation extraterrestre très avancée, qu&amp;rsquo;il appelle les Elohim.</description></item><item><title>Let's Welcome The Extraterrestrials</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/lets-welcome-the-extraterrestrials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/lets-welcome-the-extraterrestrials/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s Welcome the Extraterrestrials,&amp;rdquo; the third book in the Raelian series, is a compilation of Rael&amp;rsquo;s responses to frequently asked questions post-publication of his first two books. It addresses apparent contradictions between his earlier messages, clarifies the Raelian stance on various topics, and offers insights into the beliefs and teachings of the Raelian Movement. The book delves into the origins of life on Earth, the role of the Elohim in human history, the relationship between humans and their creators, and the future of humanity in relation to extraterrestrial life.</description></item></channel></rss>