<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Theology on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/topics/theology/</link><description>Recent content in Theology on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/topics/theology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Echoes of Eden: What secrets of human potential were buried with our ancestors' memories of ET contact?</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/echoes-of-eden/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/echoes-of-eden/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Echoes of Eden&amp;rdquo; by Paul Anthony Wallis delves into the potential connections between human history and extraterrestrial contacts as depicted in ancient narratives worldwide. The book explores the idea that entities described in these stories, which we would today classify as extraterrestrial beings (ETs), have played a significant role in human history. Wallis takes the reader on a global journey, from Senate briefings in Washington DC to secret ceremonies in southern Africa, and from strange phenomena in Australia and Iraq to mysterious encounters in modern Brazil and ancient Greece.</description></item><item><title>Escaping from Eden: Does Genesis teach that the human race was created by God or engineered by ETs?</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/escaping-from-eden/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/escaping-from-eden/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Escaping from Eden&amp;rdquo; by Paul Wallis is a book that reexamines the stories of the Book of Genesis. Wallis suggests that anomalies in the text indicate we are not reading the original versions of these stories. He explores what the original narratives might have been, particularly regarding human origins, which he believes were almost obliterated from the Hebrew Scriptures in the 6th century BC and suppressed in Christian writings in the 2nd and 3rd centuries AD.</description></item><item><title>Sefaria: A Living Library of Torah</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/sefaria/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/sefaria/</guid><description>Sefaria, founded in 2011 by journalist Joshua Foer and Brett Lockspeiser, a former product manager at Google, is a remarkable digital library of Jewish texts. Its name, derived from the Hebrew words &amp;ldquo;sefer&amp;rdquo; (book) and &amp;ldquo;sifria&amp;rdquo; (library), encapsulates its mission to be a comprehensive, accessible repository of Jewish knowledge​​​​.
The platform is designed as an open-source, free-content digital library, offering a wide array of Jewish texts in original languages like Hebrew, Aramaic, and Judeo-Arabic, along with translations.</description></item><item><title>The Bible Is Not a Sacred Book — The Great Deception</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/the-bible-is-not-a-sacred-book/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/the-bible-is-not-a-sacred-book/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;La Bibbia non è un libro sacro. Il grande inganno&amp;rdquo; (&amp;ldquo;The Bible is Not a Sacred Book. The Great Deception&amp;rdquo;) by Mauro Biglino presents a controversial view of the Bible, particularly the Old Testament. Biglino argues that the Bible does not contain a spiritually understood divinity and that there is no worship directed towards God in it. He questions the traditional understanding of the Bible, raising issues like the multiple versions of the Bible, the unknown authors and time of its writing, the real nature of the Tree of Life, and the idea that humans are genetically modified organisms (GMOs).</description></item><item><title>The Bible of La Pleiade</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/la-bible-of-la-pleiade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/la-bible-of-la-pleiade/</guid><description>The &amp;ldquo;La Bible: Ancient Testament (tome 1 et 2)&amp;rdquo; from La Pléiade publisher, translated by Édouard Dhorme, Franck Michaéli, and Antoine Guillaumont, offers a comprehensive look at the Old Testament.
Tome 1: This volume includes the Pentateuch, which contains narratives of the creation, early prophets, and the Exodus. It also covers historical books such as Joshua, the books of Samuel, the books of Kings, Chronicles, Ezra, Nehemiah, and the books of the Maccabees.</description></item><item><title>The Kabbalah: Law and Mysticism in the Jewish Tradition</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/the-kabbalah-law-and-mysticism-in-the-jewish-tradition-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/the-kabbalah-law-and-mysticism-in-the-jewish-tradition-/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The Kabbalah: Law and Mysticism in the Jewish Tradition&amp;rdquo; (simply &amp;ldquo;La Kabbale&amp;rdquo; in French, its original title) by Alexandre Safran is a comprehensive exploration of Jewish mysticism and tradition, transcending a purely analytical study of Jewish esotericism. The book offers a complete and harmonious vision of the Hebrew tradition, tracing its evolution from its beginnings to the present day. Safran highlights the unity and continuity within Jewish tradition, emphasizing how divisions between law and freedom, intelligence and sensitivity, appear artificial in the context of Kabbalah.</description></item><item><title>The Naked Bible</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/the-naked-bible/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/the-naked-bible/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The Naked Bible&amp;rdquo; by Mauro Biglino and Giorgio Cattaneo is a reinterpretation of the Bible, stripping it of traditional interpretations. According to Biglino&amp;rsquo;s research, once these layers are removed, the Bible reveals a very different narrative, one that does not involve a spiritual, almighty, and all-knowing God. The book challenges the very concept of eternity as traditionally understood in biblical context. This reinterpretation is a result of a comprehensive interview between Mauro Biglino and journalist Giorgio Cattaneo, exploring Biglino&amp;rsquo;s extensive research on the subject​</description></item><item><title>The Scars of Eden: Has humanity confused the idea of God with memories of ET contact?</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/the-scars-of-eden/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/the-scars-of-eden/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The Scars of Eden&amp;rdquo; by Paul Wallis, following his previous work &amp;ldquo;Escaping from Eden,&amp;rdquo; explores whether the world&amp;rsquo;s mythologies, including the Bible, are actual accounts of God or ancestral memories of extraterrestrial contact. Wallis delves into ancient stories of contact, adaptation, and abduction, relating them to contemporary experiences worldwide. He includes insights from ancestral voices, modern experiencers, and renowned researchers, discussing recent disclosures from the US Navy, the Pentagon, and French Intelligence.</description></item></channel></rss>