<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>manifesto on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/medium/manifesto/</link><description>Recent content in manifesto on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/medium/manifesto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cyberparadism Manifesto</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/cyberparadism-manifesto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/cyberparadism-manifesto/</guid><description>The Cyberparadism Manifesto, found on GitHub, outlines a vision for a future shaped by the positive potential of technology and scientific progress. At its core, Cyberparadism focuses on using technology to enhance the human experience, promote sustainability, and foster a collective sense of purpose and responsibility. It is not a political or economic manifesto, but rather an aesthetic declaration that seeks to inspire and stimulate imagination. The manifesto embraces the idea that technology can create a world of abundance, equity, and harmony with nature.</description></item><item><title>The Engagement</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/the-engagement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/the-engagement/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The Engagement&amp;rdquo; is a proposal addressing the Israeli-Palestinian conflict. It suggests that the conflict in the Holy Land, primarily between Jewish and Palestinian communities, represents a clash of civilizations rooted in a deep and intensive encounter between Western (Judeo-Christian) and Middle Eastern (Arab-Muslim) cultures. The proposal argues that about 80-90% of Palestinians are descendants of the People of Israel, who remained in the country after the destruction of the Second Jewish Temple and were forced to convert to Islam.</description></item><item><title>The Techno-Optimist Manifesto</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/the-techno-optimist-manifesto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/the-techno-optimist-manifesto/</guid><description>The Techno-Optimist Manifesto presents a vision of a future where technology is the driving force behind societal progress and human well-being. It challenges the pervasive narrative that technology causes harm, such as job loss, environmental degradation, and societal ills, arguing instead that technology has been, and should continue to be, a source of human advancement and achievement.
Central to the manifesto is the belief that societies, like sharks, must continue to grow or face decline.</description></item></channel></rss>