<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fiction on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/topics/fiction/</link><description>Recent content in Fiction on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/topics/fiction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Creators: The Past</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/creators-the-past/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/creators-the-past/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Creators: The Past&amp;rdquo; is an Italian science fiction fantasy film directed by Piergiuseppe Zaia, who also co-wrote the screenplay with Eleonora Fani and composed the soundtrack. The film features a notable cast, including Eleonora Fani, Jennifer Mischiati, Bruce Payne, and guest appearances by Gérard Depardieu and William Shatner. The plot revolves around the manipulation of mankind&amp;rsquo;s destiny by a race of powerful extraterrestrials known as the Creators. It was announced as the first part of a planned trilogy, with the next two installments being &amp;ldquo;Creators: The Present&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Creators: The Future.</description></item><item><title>Hard to Be a God</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/hard-to-be-a-god/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/hard-to-be-a-god/</guid><description>Hard to Be a God (1989) is a West German-Soviet-French-Swiss science fiction film directed by Peter Fleischmann, based on the novel of the same name by Arkady and Boris Strugatsky. The film is set on a distant planet that mirrors Earth&amp;rsquo;s Middle Ages, where society has not progressed beyond a primitive, feudal state. This alien world is being observed by Earth scientists posing as noble feudal lords.
The central character, Anton, is one of the scientists sent from Earth.</description></item><item><title>Jurassic World</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/jurassic-world/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/jurassic-world/</guid><description>Jurassic World is a 2015 American science fiction adventure film and the fourth installment in the Jurassic Park franchise. Directed by Colin Trevorrow and written by Trevorrow, Derek Connolly, Rick Jaffa, and Amanda Silver, the film is set 22 years after the events of the original Jurassic Park and takes place on the same fictional Central American island of Isla Nublar, off Costa Rica&amp;rsquo;s Pacific Coast.
In Jurassic World, the island has been transformed into a fully functioning dinosaur theme park, as originally envisioned by John Hammond.</description></item><item><title>Terranigma</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/terranigma/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/terranigma/</guid><description>Terranigma, developed by Quintet (株式会社クインテット) and published by Enix for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System (SNES), is a 1995 action role-playing game with a rich narrative and thematic depth. The game&amp;rsquo;s story centers around Ark, a mischievous teenager from the underground village of Crysta. Ark&amp;rsquo;s journey begins when his curiosity triggers a series of events leading to the resurrection of life on a previously barren Earth.
The game unfolds across four main chapters.</description></item><item><title>The Possibility of an Island</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/the-possibility-of-an-island/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/the-possibility-of-an-island/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The Possibility of an Island&amp;rdquo; (French: La Possibilité d&amp;rsquo;une île), a novel published in 2005 by French novelist Michel Houellebecq, is set within a cloning cult that bears resemblance to the real-world Raëlian movement. The narrative revolves around three main characters: Daniel, a successful comedian disillusioned with his hedonistic lifestyle and the state of society, and his two clones, who lead a hermit-like existence in a post-apocalyptic future. This future world is depicted as one where the human species, ravaged by climate change and nuclear war, has either regressed to hunter-gatherer societies or is on the brink of extinction.</description></item></channel></rss>