<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mormonism on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/topics/mormonism/</link><description>Recent content in Mormonism on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/topics/mormonism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Book of Abraham</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-abraham/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-abraham/</guid><description>The Book of Abraham is a work that is considered scripture by the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints (LDS Church). It is believed to be an inspired translation of writings attributed to Abraham. The book was first published in 1842 and later canonized as part of the LDS Church&amp;rsquo;s Pearl of Great Price in 1880.
The content of the Book of Abraham includes a narrative of Abraham&amp;rsquo;s life, his travels to Canaan and Egypt, and visions he received concerning the universe, a pre-mortal existence, and the creation of the world.</description></item><item><title>Book of Mormon</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-mormon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-mormon/</guid><description>The Book of Mormon, foundational to the Latter Day Saint movement, is a religious text published by Joseph Smith in 1830. Smith described it as a translation of golden plates shown to him by an angel, Moroni. The narrative details the history of ancient peoples in the Americas, focusing on their spiritual journey and teachings, with a pivotal event being the appearance of Jesus Christ post-resurrection. It&amp;rsquo;s considered by adherents as a complementary scripture to the Bible, offering insights into Christian theology and moral teachings.</description></item></channel></rss>