<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>web-project on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/medium/web-project/</link><description>Recent content in web-project on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/medium/web-project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mazzaroth | The Alpha and the Omega</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/mazzaroth-dot-com/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/mazzaroth-dot-com/</guid><description>Jim A. Cornwell&amp;rsquo;s website, mazzaroth.com, offers a detailed exploration of the interplay between the zodiac, biblical narratives, and ancient civilizations. It delves into the correlations of zodiac symbols with biblical patriarchs, interprets the creation story in Genesis in relation to astronomical events, and examines the historical and astronomical connections to various periods, such as the Bronze Age and Egyptian Dynasties. The site also explores themes like the New Age, the Antichrist, and biblical prophecies of tribulation, linking these concepts to astronomical interpretations and the concept of completeness symbolized by the number twelve.</description></item><item><title>Space a Go Go (archived website)</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/space-a-gogo-dot-com/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/space-a-gogo-dot-com/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Space a Go Go&amp;rdquo; is a website that presents the theory that humans were created by extraterrestrials, drawing on archaeological evidence and interpretations of ancient texts. It suggests that UFOs are piloted by extraterrestrials who have been trying to make their existence known to humanity. The site references the work of Zecharia Sitchin, who claimed that ancient clay tablets from Iraq recorded the creation of humans by extraterrestrials. It also mentions geneticists questioning the natural evolution theory, suggesting that human genetic code indicates an extraterrestrial author.</description></item><item><title>The Pillar of Enoch</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/pillar-of-enoch-dot-com/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/pillar-of-enoch-dot-com/</guid><description>Helena Lehman&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Pillar of Enoch&amp;rdquo; website is a resource for those interested in Judeo-Christian spiritual truths, ancient history, and future prophecies related to signs in the heavens as connected to Bible prophecy. The site features her &amp;ldquo;Language of God Book Series,&amp;rdquo; which explores biblical allegory and symbolism. The series delves into the prophetic imagery of the Bible, sacred monuments like the Great Pyramid and Solomon&amp;rsquo;s Temple, and connections to constellations like Orion.</description></item></channel></rss>