<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Resources on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/</link><description>Recent content in Resources on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Gentleman’s Joyous Esotericism: Jean Sendy Above and Beyond the Ancient Aliens</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/a-gentlemans-joyous-esotericism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/a-gentlemans-joyous-esotericism/</guid><description>In his paper &amp;ldquo;A Gentleman’s Joyous Esotericism: Jean Sendy Above and Beyond the Ancient Aliens,&amp;rdquo; Stefano Bigliardi discusses the work of Jean Sendy, a French esoteric writer who explored the idea of ancient astronauts and extraterrestrial intervention in human history. Bigliardi provides an overview of Sendy&amp;rsquo;s life and work, including his theories on the origins of humanity, the influence of extraterrestrial beings, and the possible connections between various mythologies and ancient cultures.</description></item><item><title>Alternative History VS Mainstream History or War on Facts</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/alternative-history-s-mainstream-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/alternative-history-s-mainstream-history/</guid><description>The video &amp;ldquo;Alternative History VS Mainstream History or War on Facts&amp;rdquo; made by Versadoco delves into the complexities of scientific paradigms in the context of historical studies. It discusses how these paradigms, often linked to career advancements, can make it challenging for archaeologists to question dominant perspectives. The evolving nature of science, seen not as a dogma but as an instrument to understand reality, plays a critical role in shaping our understanding of history, which itself is fragmented and open to interpretation.</description></item><item><title>Ancient Apocalypse</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/ancient-apocalypse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/ancient-apocalypse/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Ancient Apocalypse,&amp;rdquo; a 2022 Netflix documentary series hosted by British writer Graham Hancock, presents a series of pseudoarchaeological theories about an advanced civilization that existed during the last ice age. The series, produced by ITN Productions and highly watched upon release, suggests that this civilization was destroyed in a cataclysm and its survivors introduced agriculture, monumental architecture, and astronomy to hunter-gatherers around the world. Hancock contends that various ancient monuments are evidence of this civilization and accuses archaeologists of ignoring or covering up this alleged evidence.</description></item><item><title>Avesta</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-enoch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-enoch/</guid><description>The Avesta is the holy scripture of Zoroastrianism, one of the world&amp;rsquo;s oldest monotheistic religions. Composed over several centuries, its authorship is traditionally attributed to the prophet Zoroaster (from the Greek transcription Ζωροάστρης, Zōroastrēs), also known as Zarathustra (from the Avestan 𐬰𐬀𐬭𐬀𐬚𐬎𐬱𐬙𐬭𐬀, transliterated Zaraθuštra) but it likely includes contributions from many authors. The Avesta consists of various parts, including hymns, liturgical texts, mythological lore, moral guidance, and prayers. These texts are central to Zoroastrian religious practice and philosophy, emphasizing the cosmic struggle between good and evil.</description></item><item><title>Bahaipedia</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/bahaipedia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/bahaipedia/</guid><description>Bahaipedia is an independent, collaboratively edited encyclopedia focused on the Bahá&amp;rsquo;í Faith. Initiated in March 2007 by David Haslip, it aims to connect readers with primary source materials foundational to Bahá&amp;rsquo;í teachings and history. The site, powered by MediaWiki, features over 18,481 pages, edited by volunteers from diverse backgrounds. Bahaipedia includes sister projects like Bahaimedia for media storage, Bahaiworks for historical documents, and Bahai9.com for quotes and resources. The primary server is in Virginia, with secondary servers globally.</description></item><item><title>Barton Cylinder</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/barton-cylinder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/barton-cylinder/</guid><description>The Barton Cylinder, also known as CBS 8383, is a significant artifact of Sumerian literature and mythology. Dating from the mid to late 3rd millennium BCE, approximately around 2400 BCE, it is a clay cylinder inscribed with a Sumerian cuneiform text. The cylinder was discovered in 1889 at the site of Nippur during excavations by the University of Pennsylvania and is currently housed in the University of Pennsylvania Museum of Archaeology and Anthropology.</description></item><item><title>Book of Abraham</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-abraham/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-abraham/</guid><description>The Book of Abraham is a work that is considered scripture by the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints (LDS Church). It is believed to be an inspired translation of writings attributed to Abraham. The book was first published in 1842 and later canonized as part of the LDS Church&amp;rsquo;s Pearl of Great Price in 1880.
The content of the Book of Abraham includes a narrative of Abraham&amp;rsquo;s life, his travels to Canaan and Egypt, and visions he received concerning the universe, a pre-mortal existence, and the creation of the world.</description></item><item><title>Book of Enoch</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/avesta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/avesta/</guid><description>The Book of Enoch, also known as 1 Enoch, is an ancient Hebrew apocalyptic religious text traditionally attributed to the patriarch Enoch. It contains unique material on the origins of demons and Nephilim, the reasons why some angels fell from heaven, and a prophetic exposition of the thousand-year reign of the Messiah. The oldest sections are estimated to date from 300–200 BC, with the latest part around 100 BC. The text, thought to be originally written in Aramaic or Hebrew, is found in various fragments, including the Dead Sea Scrolls.</description></item><item><title>Book of Mormon</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-mormon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-mormon/</guid><description>The Book of Mormon, foundational to the Latter Day Saint movement, is a religious text published by Joseph Smith in 1830. Smith described it as a translation of golden plates shown to him by an angel, Moroni. The narrative details the history of ancient peoples in the Americas, focusing on their spiritual journey and teachings, with a pivotal event being the appearance of Jesus Christ post-resurrection. It&amp;rsquo;s considered by adherents as a complementary scripture to the Bible, offering insights into Christian theology and moral teachings.</description></item><item><title>Creators: The Past</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/creators-the-past/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/creators-the-past/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Creators: The Past&amp;rdquo; is an Italian science fiction fantasy film directed by Piergiuseppe Zaia, who also co-wrote the screenplay with Eleonora Fani and composed the soundtrack. The film features a notable cast, including Eleonora Fani, Jennifer Mischiati, Bruce Payne, and guest appearances by Gérard Depardieu and William Shatner. The plot revolves around the manipulation of mankind&amp;rsquo;s destiny by a race of powerful extraterrestrials known as the Creators. It was announced as the first part of a planned trilogy, with the next two installments being &amp;ldquo;Creators: The Present&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Creators: The Future.</description></item></channel></rss>