<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Astrological ages on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/topics/astrological-ages/</link><description>Recent content in Astrological ages on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/topics/astrological-ages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hamlet's Mill: An Essay Investigating the Origins of Human Knowledge and Its Transmission Through Myth</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/hamlets-mill/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/hamlets-mill/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Hamlet&amp;rsquo;s Mill: An Essay Investigating the Origins of Human Knowledge and Its Transmission Through Myth,&amp;rdquo; written by Giorgio de Santillana and Hertha von Dechend, presents the argument that ancient mythologies contain sophisticated knowledge of the precession of the equinoxes. This knowledge, they argue, indicates a Neolithic discovery and a long-lived Megalithic civilization of remarkable sophistication, particularly in astronomical observation. The authors suggest that this civilization&amp;rsquo;s knowledge was encoded in myths, often represented by a millstone and a young protagonist, which they interpret primarily through the lens of archaeoastronomy.</description></item><item><title>Mazzaroth | The Alpha and the Omega</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/mazzaroth-dot-com/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/mazzaroth-dot-com/</guid><description>Jim A. Cornwell&amp;rsquo;s website, mazzaroth.com, offers a detailed exploration of the interplay between the zodiac, biblical narratives, and ancient civilizations. It delves into the correlations of zodiac symbols with biblical patriarchs, interprets the creation story in Genesis in relation to astronomical events, and examines the historical and astronomical connections to various periods, such as the Bronze Age and Egyptian Dynasties. The site also explores themes like the New Age, the Antichrist, and biblical prophecies of tribulation, linking these concepts to astronomical interpretations and the concept of completeness symbolized by the number twelve.</description></item><item><title>Mazzaroth; or, The constellations</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/mazzaroth-rolleston/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/mazzaroth-rolleston/</guid><description>Frances Rolleston&amp;rsquo;s book, &amp;ldquo;Mazzaroth; or, The Constellations,&amp;rdquo; explores the significance and symbolism of the constellations in the context of divine revelation and biblical prophecy. She contends that the constellations hold a deeper, spiritual meaning that has been obscured by associations with pagan mythology and a lack of understanding of their original intent.
Rolleston argues that the constellations and their names, which are known worldwide and throughout history, point to a common origin both for humanity and these celestial symbols.</description></item><item><title>The Coming Of The Gods</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/the-coming-of-the-gods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/the-coming-of-the-gods/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The Coming of the Gods&amp;rdquo; by Jean Sendy explores the concept that advanced extraterrestrial civilizations, referred to as &amp;ldquo;gods,&amp;rdquo; have been visiting Earth for thousands of years, significantly influencing human history and religious beliefs. Sendy attributes many technological and cultural advancements, the creation of religious beliefs, and the inspiration for ancient myths and legends to these extraterrestrial beings. He suggests that these interactions between humans and these &amp;ldquo;gods&amp;rdquo; have occurred in various forms, including direct communication and the performance of miracles.</description></item><item><title>The Gospel in the Stars</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/the-gospels-in-the-stars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/the-gospels-in-the-stars/</guid><description>Joseph A. Seiss&amp;rsquo; book &amp;ldquo;The Gospel in the Stars&amp;rdquo; presents a unique interpretation of the constellations, suggesting that they carry a divine message relating to the gospel of Jesus Christ. Seiss, an American pastor and author, proposes that the arrangement and symbolism of the constellations have been used throughout human history as a means to convey knowledge and wisdom, particularly concerning the nature of God and the plan of salvation.</description></item><item><title>The Moon: Outpost of the Gods</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/the-moon-outpost-of-the-gods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/the-moon-outpost-of-the-gods/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The Moon: Outpost of the Gods&amp;rdquo; (1968), also known as &amp;ldquo;La lune clé de la Bible&amp;rdquo; by Jean Sendy, presents a unique interpretation of the biblical text, particularly the Book of Genesis. Sendy argues that the word &amp;ldquo;Elohim&amp;rdquo; in Hebrew Genesis, traditionally translated as &amp;ldquo;God,&amp;rdquo; should be interpreted in the plural form as &amp;ldquo;Gods.&amp;rdquo; He suggests that these &amp;ldquo;Gods&amp;rdquo; were actually space travelers or alien humanoids who colonized Earth, later becoming the &amp;ldquo;angels&amp;rdquo; in human memory.</description></item><item><title>The Revelation of the Pyramids</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/the-revelation-of-the-pyramid/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/the-revelation-of-the-pyramid/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The Revelation of the Pyramids,&amp;rdquo; a French documentary directed by Patrice Pooyard and released in 2010, delves into pseudo-historical theories proposed by Jacques Grimault. Grimault&amp;rsquo;s unpublished works suggest a slow cycle of geological changes on Earth, including shifts in magnetic poles, causing catastrophic events every 26,000 years. He theorizes that an ancient civilization, predating ours, was destroyed by these catastrophes, and that they built the Pyramids of Giza and other ancient structures.</description></item><item><title>Those Gods Who Made Heaven and Earth: The Evidence for Alien Visitors to Earth before the Dawn of History</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/those-gods-who-made-heaven-and-earth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/those-gods-who-made-heaven-and-earth/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Those Gods Who Made Heaven and Earth: The Evidence for Alien Visitors to Earth before the Dawn of History&amp;rdquo; by Jean Sendy is a book that explores the possibility of extraterrestrial influence on ancient human civilizations. Sendy argues that many myths, legends, and religious texts of ancient cultures, including those of the Sumerians, Egyptians, and Mayans, contain references to extraterrestrial visitors, which he interprets as evidence of real encounters between humans and aliens.</description></item></channel></rss>