<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ресурсы on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/</link><description>Recent content in Ресурсы on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Gentleman’s Joyous Esotericism: Jean Sendy Above and Beyond the Ancient Aliens</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/a-gentlemans-joyous-esotericism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/a-gentlemans-joyous-esotericism/</guid><description>In his paper &amp;ldquo;A Gentleman’s Joyous Esotericism: Jean Sendy Above and Beyond the Ancient Aliens,&amp;rdquo; Stefano Bigliardi discusses the work of Jean Sendy, a French esoteric writer who explored the idea of ancient astronauts and extraterrestrial intervention in human history. Bigliardi provides an overview of Sendy&amp;rsquo;s life and work, including his theories on the origins of humanity, the influence of extraterrestrial beings, and the possible connections between various mythologies and ancient cultures.</description></item><item><title>Alternative History VS Mainstream History or War on Facts</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/alternative-history-s-mainstream-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/alternative-history-s-mainstream-history/</guid><description>The video &amp;ldquo;Alternative History VS Mainstream History or War on Facts&amp;rdquo; made by Versadoco delves into the complexities of scientific paradigms in the context of historical studies. It discusses how these paradigms, often linked to career advancements, can make it challenging for archaeologists to question dominant perspectives. The evolving nature of science, seen not as a dogma but as an instrument to understand reality, plays a critical role in shaping our understanding of history, which itself is fragmented and open to interpretation.</description></item><item><title>Ancient Apocalypse</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/ancient-apocalypse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/ancient-apocalypse/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Ancient Apocalypse,&amp;rdquo; a 2022 Netflix documentary series hosted by British writer Graham Hancock, presents a series of pseudoarchaeological theories about an advanced civilization that existed during the last ice age. The series, produced by ITN Productions and highly watched upon release, suggests that this civilization was destroyed in a cataclysm and its survivors introduced agriculture, monumental architecture, and astronomy to hunter-gatherers around the world. Hancock contends that various ancient monuments are evidence of this civilization and accuses archaeologists of ignoring or covering up this alleged evidence.</description></item><item><title>Creators: The Past</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/creators-the-past/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/creators-the-past/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Creators: The Past&amp;rdquo; is an Italian science fiction fantasy film directed by Piergiuseppe Zaia, who also co-wrote the screenplay with Eleonora Fani and composed the soundtrack. The film features a notable cast, including Eleonora Fani, Jennifer Mischiati, Bruce Payne, and guest appearances by Gérard Depardieu and William Shatner. The plot revolves around the manipulation of mankind&amp;rsquo;s destiny by a race of powerful extraterrestrials known as the Creators. It was announced as the first part of a planned trilogy, with the next two installments being &amp;ldquo;Creators: The Present&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Creators: The Future.</description></item><item><title>Cyberparadism Manifesto</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/cyberparadism-manifesto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/cyberparadism-manifesto/</guid><description>The Cyberparadism Manifesto, found on GitHub, outlines a vision for a future shaped by the positive potential of technology and scientific progress. At its core, Cyberparadism focuses on using technology to enhance the human experience, promote sustainability, and foster a collective sense of purpose and responsibility. It is not a political or economic manifesto, but rather an aesthetic declaration that seeks to inspire and stimulate imagination. The manifesto embraces the idea that technology can create a world of abundance, equity, and harmony with nature.</description></item><item><title>Echoes of Eden: What secrets of human potential were buried with our ancestors' memories of ET contact?</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/echoes-of-eden/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/echoes-of-eden/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Echoes of Eden&amp;rdquo; by Paul Anthony Wallis delves into the potential connections between human history and extraterrestrial contacts as depicted in ancient narratives worldwide. The book explores the idea that entities described in these stories, which we would today classify as extraterrestrial beings (ETs), have played a significant role in human history. Wallis takes the reader on a global journey, from Senate briefings in Washington DC to secret ceremonies in southern Africa, and from strange phenomena in Australia and Iraq to mysterious encounters in modern Brazil and ancient Greece.</description></item><item><title>Epic of Gilgamesh</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/epic-of-gilgamesh/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/epic-of-gilgamesh/</guid><description>The Epic of Gilgamesh is an ancient Mesopotamian poem, regarded as one of the earliest great works of literature. It narrates the adventures of Gilgamesh, the historical king of Uruk, and his quest for immortality, exploring themes of friendship, the human condition, and the fear of death. The epic, written in cuneiform on clay tablets, dates back to the early 3rd millennium BCE.
The story begins with the introduction of Gilgamesh, two-thirds god and one-third human, who is a tyrannical king of Uruk.</description></item><item><title>Escaping from Eden: Does Genesis teach that the human race was created by God or engineered by ETs?</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/escaping-from-eden/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/escaping-from-eden/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Escaping from Eden&amp;rdquo; by Paul Wallis is a book that reexamines the stories of the Book of Genesis. Wallis suggests that anomalies in the text indicate we are not reading the original versions of these stories. He explores what the original narratives might have been, particularly regarding human origins, which he believes were almost obliterated from the Hebrew Scriptures in the 6th century BC and suppressed in Christian writings in the 2nd and 3rd centuries AD.</description></item><item><title>Extraterrestrials Took Me To Their Planet</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/extraterrestrials-took-me-to-their-planet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/extraterrestrials-took-me-to-their-planet/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Extraterrestrials Took Me to Their Planet&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Claude Vorilhon, also known as Raël, the founder of the Raëlian Movement. The book is a sequel to Raël&amp;rsquo;s first book, &amp;ldquo;The Book Which Tells the Truth,&amp;rdquo; and it expands on the ideas and teachings presented in that work. In &amp;ldquo;Extraterrestrials Took Me to Their Planet,&amp;rdquo; Raël describes his experiences with extraterrestrial beings, whom he refers to as the Elohim.</description></item><item><title>Fingerprints of the Gods: The Evidence of Earth's Lost Civilization</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/fingerprints-of-the-gods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/fingerprints-of-the-gods/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Fingerprints of the Gods: The Evidence of Earth&amp;rsquo;s Lost Civilization&amp;rdquo; by Graham Hancock, published in 1995, explores the hypothesis of a highly advanced civilization existing in prehistory, serving as the progenitor of all known ancient civilizations. Hancock proposes that this civilization, centered around Antarctica, ended catastrophically at the end of the last ice age but passed on significant knowledge in astronomy, architecture, and mathematics. The evidence for this lost civilization, according to Hancock, is found in ancient Egypt and American civilizations like the Olmec, Aztec, and Maya.</description></item></channel></rss>