<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Age of Aquarius on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/topics/age-of-aquarius/</link><description>Recent content in Age of Aquarius on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/topics/age-of-aquarius/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Gentleman’s Joyous Esotericism: Jean Sendy Above and Beyond the Ancient Aliens</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/a-gentlemans-joyous-esotericism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/a-gentlemans-joyous-esotericism/</guid><description>In his paper &amp;ldquo;A Gentleman’s Joyous Esotericism: Jean Sendy Above and Beyond the Ancient Aliens,&amp;rdquo; Stefano Bigliardi discusses the work of Jean Sendy, a French esoteric writer who explored the idea of ancient astronauts and extraterrestrial intervention in human history. Bigliardi provides an overview of Sendy&amp;rsquo;s life and work, including his theories on the origins of humanity, the influence of extraterrestrial beings, and the possible connections between various mythologies and ancient cultures.</description></item><item><title>Ancient Apocalypse</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/ancient-apocalypse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/ancient-apocalypse/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Ancient Apocalypse,&amp;rdquo; a 2022 Netflix documentary series hosted by British writer Graham Hancock, presents a series of pseudoarchaeological theories about an advanced civilization that existed during the last ice age. The series, produced by ITN Productions and highly watched upon release, suggests that this civilization was destroyed in a cataclysm and its survivors introduced agriculture, monumental architecture, and astronomy to hunter-gatherers around the world. Hancock contends that various ancient monuments are evidence of this civilization and accuses archaeologists of ignoring or covering up this alleged evidence.</description></item><item><title>Creators: The Past</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/creators-the-past/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/creators-the-past/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Creators: The Past&amp;rdquo; is an Italian science fiction fantasy film directed by Piergiuseppe Zaia, who also co-wrote the screenplay with Eleonora Fani and composed the soundtrack. The film features a notable cast, including Eleonora Fani, Jennifer Mischiati, Bruce Payne, and guest appearances by Gérard Depardieu and William Shatner. The plot revolves around the manipulation of mankind&amp;rsquo;s destiny by a race of powerful extraterrestrials known as the Creators. It was announced as the first part of a planned trilogy, with the next two installments being &amp;ldquo;Creators: The Present&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Creators: The Future.</description></item><item><title>Cyberparadism Manifesto</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/cyberparadism-manifesto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/cyberparadism-manifesto/</guid><description>The Cyberparadism Manifesto, found on GitHub, outlines a vision for a future shaped by the positive potential of technology and scientific progress. At its core, Cyberparadism focuses on using technology to enhance the human experience, promote sustainability, and foster a collective sense of purpose and responsibility. It is not a political or economic manifesto, but rather an aesthetic declaration that seeks to inspire and stimulate imagination. The manifesto embraces the idea that technology can create a world of abundance, equity, and harmony with nature.</description></item><item><title>Extraterrestrials Took Me To Their Planet</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/extraterrestrials-took-me-to-their-planet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/extraterrestrials-took-me-to-their-planet/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Extraterrestrials Took Me to Their Planet&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Claude Vorilhon, also known as Raël, the founder of the Raëlian Movement. The book is a sequel to Raël&amp;rsquo;s first book, &amp;ldquo;The Book Which Tells the Truth,&amp;rdquo; and it expands on the ideas and teachings presented in that work. In &amp;ldquo;Extraterrestrials Took Me to Their Planet,&amp;rdquo; Raël describes his experiences with extraterrestrial beings, whom he refers to as the Elohim.</description></item><item><title>Fingerprints of the Gods: The Evidence of Earth's Lost Civilization</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/fingerprints-of-the-gods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/fingerprints-of-the-gods/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Fingerprints of the Gods: The Evidence of Earth&amp;rsquo;s Lost Civilization&amp;rdquo; by Graham Hancock, published in 1995, explores the hypothesis of a highly advanced civilization existing in prehistory, serving as the progenitor of all known ancient civilizations. Hancock proposes that this civilization, centered around Antarctica, ended catastrophically at the end of the last ice age but passed on significant knowledge in astronomy, architecture, and mathematics. The evidence for this lost civilization, according to Hancock, is found in ancient Egypt and American civilizations like the Olmec, Aztec, and Maya.</description></item><item><title>Jurassic World</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/jurassic-world/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/jurassic-world/</guid><description>Jurassic World is a 2015 American science fiction adventure film and the fourth installment in the Jurassic Park franchise. Directed by Colin Trevorrow and written by Trevorrow, Derek Connolly, Rick Jaffa, and Amanda Silver, the film is set 22 years after the events of the original Jurassic Park and takes place on the same fictional Central American island of Isla Nublar, off Costa Rica&amp;rsquo;s Pacific Coast.
In Jurassic World, the island has been transformed into a fully functioning dinosaur theme park, as originally envisioned by John Hammond.</description></item><item><title>Let's Welcome The Extraterrestrials</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/lets-welcome-the-extraterrestrials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/lets-welcome-the-extraterrestrials/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s Welcome the Extraterrestrials,&amp;rdquo; the third book in the Raelian series, is a compilation of Rael&amp;rsquo;s responses to frequently asked questions post-publication of his first two books. It addresses apparent contradictions between his earlier messages, clarifies the Raelian stance on various topics, and offers insights into the beliefs and teachings of the Raelian Movement. The book delves into the origins of life on Earth, the role of the Elohim in human history, the relationship between humans and their creators, and the future of humanity in relation to extraterrestrial life.</description></item><item><title>Mazzaroth; or, The constellations</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/mazzaroth-rolleston/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/mazzaroth-rolleston/</guid><description>Frances Rolleston&amp;rsquo;s book, &amp;ldquo;Mazzaroth; or, The Constellations,&amp;rdquo; explores the significance and symbolism of the constellations in the context of divine revelation and biblical prophecy. She contends that the constellations hold a deeper, spiritual meaning that has been obscured by associations with pagan mythology and a lack of understanding of their original intent.
Rolleston argues that the constellations and their names, which are known worldwide and throughout history, point to a common origin both for humanity and these celestial symbols.</description></item><item><title>The Book Which Tells The Truth</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/the-book-which-tells-the-truth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/the-book-which-tells-the-truth/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The Book Which Tells the Truth&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Claude Vorilhon, also known as Raël, the founder of the Raëlian Movement. The book details Raël&amp;rsquo;s claims of encounters with extraterrestrial beings and presents his beliefs and teachings. According to Raël, the extraterrestrial beings he encountered revealed to him that life on Earth was created through genetic engineering by a highly advanced civilization of extraterrestrial beings, who he refers to as the Elohim.</description></item></channel></rss>