<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Raëlism on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/topics/ra%C3%ABlism/</link><description>Recent content in Raëlism on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/topics/ra%C3%ABlism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Extraterrestrials Took Me To Their Planet</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/extraterrestrials-took-me-to-their-planet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/extraterrestrials-took-me-to-their-planet/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Extraterrestrials Took Me to Their Planet&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Claude Vorilhon, also known as Raël, the founder of the Raëlian Movement. The book is a sequel to Raël&amp;rsquo;s first book, &amp;ldquo;The Book Which Tells the Truth,&amp;rdquo; and it expands on the ideas and teachings presented in that work. In &amp;ldquo;Extraterrestrials Took Me to Their Planet,&amp;rdquo; Raël describes his experiences with extraterrestrial beings, whom he refers to as the Elohim.</description></item><item><title>Let's Welcome The Extraterrestrials</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/lets-welcome-the-extraterrestrials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/lets-welcome-the-extraterrestrials/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s Welcome the Extraterrestrials,&amp;rdquo; the third book in the Raelian series, is a compilation of Rael&amp;rsquo;s responses to frequently asked questions post-publication of his first two books. It addresses apparent contradictions between his earlier messages, clarifies the Raelian stance on various topics, and offers insights into the beliefs and teachings of the Raelian Movement. The book delves into the origins of life on Earth, the role of the Elohim in human history, the relationship between humans and their creators, and the future of humanity in relation to extraterrestrial life.</description></item><item><title>Raelian Movement | The true origin of life on Earth: Extraterrestrials created us in their image</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/rael-dot-org/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/rael-dot-org/</guid><description>The Raelian Movement, founded in 1974, centers on the teachings of Rael, who claims to have encountered the Elohim, a group of scientists purported to have created humanity. The movement has grown to over 130,000 members across more than 120 countries. It focuses on spreading the Elohim&amp;rsquo;s message and building an embassy for them on Earth, as detailed in Rael&amp;rsquo;s teachings. This non-profit organization is funded by its members, emphasizing a vision of a world where science is paramount and violence is eradicated.</description></item><item><title>Space a Go Go (archived website)</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/space-a-gogo-dot-com/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/space-a-gogo-dot-com/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Space a Go Go&amp;rdquo; is a website that presents the theory that humans were created by extraterrestrials, drawing on archaeological evidence and interpretations of ancient texts. It suggests that UFOs are piloted by extraterrestrials who have been trying to make their existence known to humanity. The site references the work of Zecharia Sitchin, who claimed that ancient clay tablets from Iraq recorded the creation of humans by extraterrestrials. It also mentions geneticists questioning the natural evolution theory, suggesting that human genetic code indicates an extraterrestrial author.</description></item><item><title>The Book Which Tells The Truth</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/the-book-which-tells-the-truth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/the-book-which-tells-the-truth/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The Book Which Tells the Truth&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Claude Vorilhon, also known as Raël, the founder of the Raëlian Movement. The book details Raël&amp;rsquo;s claims of encounters with extraterrestrial beings and presents his beliefs and teachings. According to Raël, the extraterrestrial beings he encountered revealed to him that life on Earth was created through genetic engineering by a highly advanced civilization of extraterrestrial beings, who he refers to as the Elohim.</description></item><item><title>The Possibility of an Island</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/the-possibility-of-an-island/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/the-possibility-of-an-island/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The Possibility of an Island&amp;rdquo; (French: La Possibilité d&amp;rsquo;une île), a novel published in 2005 by French novelist Michel Houellebecq, is set within a cloning cult that bears resemblance to the real-world Raëlian movement. The narrative revolves around three main characters: Daniel, a successful comedian disillusioned with his hedonistic lifestyle and the state of society, and his two clones, who lead a hermit-like existence in a post-apocalyptic future. This future world is depicted as one where the human species, ravaged by climate change and nuclear war, has either regressed to hunter-gatherer societies or is on the brink of extinction.</description></item></channel></rss>