<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>nonfiction-book on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/medium/nonfiction-book/</link><description>Recent content in nonfiction-book on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/medium/nonfiction-book/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Echoes of Eden: What secrets of human potential were buried with our ancestors' memories of ET contact?</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/echoes-of-eden/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/echoes-of-eden/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Echoes of Eden&amp;rdquo; by Paul Anthony Wallis delves into the potential connections between human history and extraterrestrial contacts as depicted in ancient narratives worldwide. The book explores the idea that entities described in these stories, which we would today classify as extraterrestrial beings (ETs), have played a significant role in human history. Wallis takes the reader on a global journey, from Senate briefings in Washington DC to secret ceremonies in southern Africa, and from strange phenomena in Australia and Iraq to mysterious encounters in modern Brazil and ancient Greece.</description></item><item><title>Escaping from Eden: Does Genesis teach that the human race was created by God or engineered by ETs?</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/escaping-from-eden/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/escaping-from-eden/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Escaping from Eden&amp;rdquo; by Paul Wallis is a book that reexamines the stories of the Book of Genesis. Wallis suggests that anomalies in the text indicate we are not reading the original versions of these stories. He explores what the original narratives might have been, particularly regarding human origins, which he believes were almost obliterated from the Hebrew Scriptures in the 6th century BC and suppressed in Christian writings in the 2nd and 3rd centuries AD.</description></item><item><title>Fingerprints of the Gods: The Evidence of Earth's Lost Civilization</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/fingerprints-of-the-gods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/fingerprints-of-the-gods/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Fingerprints of the Gods: The Evidence of Earth&amp;rsquo;s Lost Civilization&amp;rdquo; by Graham Hancock, published in 1995, explores the hypothesis of a highly advanced civilization existing in prehistory, serving as the progenitor of all known ancient civilizations. Hancock proposes that this civilization, centered around Antarctica, ended catastrophically at the end of the last ice age but passed on significant knowledge in astronomy, architecture, and mathematics. The evidence for this lost civilization, according to Hancock, is found in ancient Egypt and American civilizations like the Olmec, Aztec, and Maya.</description></item><item><title>Hamlet's Mill: An Essay Investigating the Origins of Human Knowledge and Its Transmission Through Myth</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/hamlets-mill/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/hamlets-mill/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Hamlet&amp;rsquo;s Mill: An Essay Investigating the Origins of Human Knowledge and Its Transmission Through Myth,&amp;rdquo; written by Giorgio de Santillana and Hertha von Dechend, presents the argument that ancient mythologies contain sophisticated knowledge of the precession of the equinoxes. This knowledge, they argue, indicates a Neolithic discovery and a long-lived Megalithic civilization of remarkable sophistication, particularly in astronomical observation. The authors suggest that this civilization&amp;rsquo;s knowledge was encoded in myths, often represented by a millstone and a young protagonist, which they interpret primarily through the lens of archaeoastronomy.</description></item><item><title>Mazzaroth; or, The constellations</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/mazzaroth-rolleston/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/mazzaroth-rolleston/</guid><description>Frances Rolleston&amp;rsquo;s book, &amp;ldquo;Mazzaroth; or, The Constellations,&amp;rdquo; explores the significance and symbolism of the constellations in the context of divine revelation and biblical prophecy. She contends that the constellations hold a deeper, spiritual meaning that has been obscured by associations with pagan mythology and a lack of understanding of their original intent.
Rolleston argues that the constellations and their names, which are known worldwide and throughout history, point to a common origin both for humanity and these celestial symbols.</description></item><item><title>Science After Babel</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/science-after-babel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/science-after-babel/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Science After Babel&amp;rdquo; by David Berlinski is a book that challenges the established norms and widely accepted theories in contemporary science. Berlinski, known for his deep learning, close reasoning, and sharp wit, critiques what he considers to be the shibboleths of modern science. These include widely accepted concepts in Darwinism, reductionism, the Standard Model of particle physics, and the idea of &amp;ldquo;talking&amp;rdquo; chimpanzees.
In his book, Berlinski questions the solidity of what is often passed off as secure scientific knowledge.</description></item><item><title>The Bible Is Not a Sacred Book — The Great Deception</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/the-bible-is-not-a-sacred-book/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/the-bible-is-not-a-sacred-book/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;La Bibbia non è un libro sacro. Il grande inganno&amp;rdquo; (&amp;ldquo;The Bible is Not a Sacred Book. The Great Deception&amp;rdquo;) by Mauro Biglino presents a controversial view of the Bible, particularly the Old Testament. Biglino argues that the Bible does not contain a spiritually understood divinity and that there is no worship directed towards God in it. He questions the traditional understanding of the Bible, raising issues like the multiple versions of the Bible, the unknown authors and time of its writing, the real nature of the Tree of Life, and the idea that humans are genetically modified organisms (GMOs).</description></item><item><title>The Coming Of The Gods</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/the-coming-of-the-gods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/the-coming-of-the-gods/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The Coming of the Gods&amp;rdquo; by Jean Sendy explores the concept that advanced extraterrestrial civilizations, referred to as &amp;ldquo;gods,&amp;rdquo; have been visiting Earth for thousands of years, significantly influencing human history and religious beliefs. Sendy attributes many technological and cultural advancements, the creation of religious beliefs, and the inspiration for ancient myths and legends to these extraterrestrial beings. He suggests that these interactions between humans and these &amp;ldquo;gods&amp;rdquo; have occurred in various forms, including direct communication and the performance of miracles.</description></item><item><title>The Devil's Delusion: Atheism and Its Scientific Pretension</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/the-devils-delusion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/the-devils-delusion/</guid><description>In &amp;ldquo;The Devil&amp;rsquo;s Delusion: Atheism and Its Scientific Pretensions,&amp;rdquo; David Berlinski mounts a vigorous critique of scientific atheism, particularly addressing the assertions made by figures like Richard Dawkins and Sam Harris. Berlinski, a secular Jew and mathematician, questions the completeness and authority of science in answering profound existential and moral questions.
Berlinski argues that the science often cited by atheists to debunk religious beliefs actually does not conclusively negate the possibility of a divine existence.</description></item><item><title>The Gospel in the Stars</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/the-gospels-in-the-stars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/the-gospels-in-the-stars/</guid><description>Joseph A. Seiss&amp;rsquo; book &amp;ldquo;The Gospel in the Stars&amp;rdquo; presents a unique interpretation of the constellations, suggesting that they carry a divine message relating to the gospel of Jesus Christ. Seiss, an American pastor and author, proposes that the arrangement and symbolism of the constellations have been used throughout human history as a means to convey knowledge and wisdom, particularly concerning the nature of God and the plan of salvation.</description></item></channel></rss>