<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>religious-text on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/medium/religious-text/</link><description>Recent content in religious-text on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/medium/religious-text/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Avesta</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-enoch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-enoch/</guid><description>The Avesta is the holy scripture of Zoroastrianism, one of the world&amp;rsquo;s oldest monotheistic religions. Composed over several centuries, its authorship is traditionally attributed to the prophet Zoroaster (from the Greek transcription Ζωροάστρης, Zōroastrēs), also known as Zarathustra (from the Avestan 𐬰𐬀𐬭𐬀𐬚𐬎𐬱𐬙𐬭𐬀, transliterated Zaraθuštra) but it likely includes contributions from many authors. The Avesta consists of various parts, including hymns, liturgical texts, mythological lore, moral guidance, and prayers. These texts are central to Zoroastrian religious practice and philosophy, emphasizing the cosmic struggle between good and evil.</description></item><item><title>Book of Abraham</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-abraham/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-abraham/</guid><description>The Book of Abraham is a work that is considered scripture by the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints (LDS Church). It is believed to be an inspired translation of writings attributed to Abraham. The book was first published in 1842 and later canonized as part of the LDS Church&amp;rsquo;s Pearl of Great Price in 1880.
The content of the Book of Abraham includes a narrative of Abraham&amp;rsquo;s life, his travels to Canaan and Egypt, and visions he received concerning the universe, a pre-mortal existence, and the creation of the world.</description></item><item><title>Book of Enoch</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/avesta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/avesta/</guid><description>The Book of Enoch, also known as 1 Enoch, is an ancient Hebrew apocalyptic religious text traditionally attributed to the patriarch Enoch. It contains unique material on the origins of demons and Nephilim, the reasons why some angels fell from heaven, and a prophetic exposition of the thousand-year reign of the Messiah. The oldest sections are estimated to date from 300–200 BC, with the latest part around 100 BC. The text, thought to be originally written in Aramaic or Hebrew, is found in various fragments, including the Dead Sea Scrolls.</description></item><item><title>Book of Mormon</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-mormon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-mormon/</guid><description>The Book of Mormon, foundational to the Latter Day Saint movement, is a religious text published by Joseph Smith in 1830. Smith described it as a translation of golden plates shown to him by an angel, Moroni. The narrative details the history of ancient peoples in the Americas, focusing on their spiritual journey and teachings, with a pivotal event being the appearance of Jesus Christ post-resurrection. It&amp;rsquo;s considered by adherents as a complementary scripture to the Bible, offering insights into Christian theology and moral teachings.</description></item><item><title>Divine Signposts</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/divine-signposts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/divine-signposts/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Divine Signposts&amp;rdquo; (大本, Ōmoto) by Onisaburo Deguchi (出口王仁三郎) is a foundational text in the spiritual and religious tradition of Ōmoto (大本), a Japanese new religious movement. Written in 1904 when Onisaburo was 33 years old, this work is one of his earliest writings and consists of 14 volumes. It lays out the basis of Ōmoto&amp;rsquo;s teachings, emphasizing the essence of faith and Onisaburo&amp;rsquo;s mission of world salvation.
This sacred text is intended to be read by Ōmoto believers as a part of their daily spiritual practice, serving as both a doctrinal book and a guide to true faith.</description></item><item><title>Kitáb-i-Aqdas</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/kitab-i-aqdas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/kitab-i-aqdas/</guid><description>The Kitáb-i-Aqdas, known as &amp;ldquo;The Most Holy Book,&amp;rdquo; is the central book of the Bahá&amp;rsquo;í Faith, written by Bahá’u’lláh, the founder of the faith. Composed in the 19th century, this sacred text lays down the laws, principles, and institutions for the Bahá&amp;rsquo;í community, and is considered the charter for a future global civilization.
The Kitáb-i-Aqdas not only provides laws and ordinances for the spiritual and daily life of believers but also articulates the administrative principles and structures of the Bahá&amp;rsquo;í Faith.</description></item><item><title>Tanakh</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/tanakh/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/tanakh/</guid><description>The Tanakh, also known as the Hebrew Bible, is the canonical collection of Jewish texts, which is also a significant part of Christian scriptures. It is divided into three sections: the Torah (Teaching or Law), the Nevi&amp;rsquo;im (Prophets), and the Ketuvim (Writings). The word &amp;ldquo;Tanakh&amp;rdquo; is an acronym derived from these three divisions.
The Torah (Law or Teaching): Also known as the Pentateuch, the Torah comprises the first five books of the Bible - Genesis, Exodus, Leviticus, Numbers, and Deuteronomy.</description></item><item><title>The Collection of Divine Messages of the Cao Đài Religion of God</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/the-collection-of-divine-messages-of-cai-dai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/the-collection-of-divine-messages-of-cai-dai/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The Collection of Divine Messages&amp;rdquo; (Thánh Ngôn Hiệp Tuyển), a key scripture of the Đạo Cao Đài religion, was compiled in 1926, encapsulating the divine teachings and revelations central to this Vietnamese religious movement. This collection is comprised of two volumes of messages, believed to be communicated by the Supreme Being and various Divine Spirits to the followers of Đạo Cao Đài.
The first volume contains several critical teachings. These include the Divine Teaching of the Jade Emperor, who introduces himself and announces the names of the twelve disciples, marking a significant moment in the development of the faith​.</description></item></channel></rss>