<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Flood Geology on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/topics/flood-geology/</link><description>Recent content in Flood Geology on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/topics/flood-geology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ancient Apocalypse</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/ancient-apocalypse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/ancient-apocalypse/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Ancient Apocalypse,&amp;rdquo; a 2022 Netflix documentary series hosted by British writer Graham Hancock, presents a series of pseudoarchaeological theories about an advanced civilization that existed during the last ice age. The series, produced by ITN Productions and highly watched upon release, suggests that this civilization was destroyed in a cataclysm and its survivors introduced agriculture, monumental architecture, and astronomy to hunter-gatherers around the world. Hancock contends that various ancient monuments are evidence of this civilization and accuses archaeologists of ignoring or covering up this alleged evidence.</description></item><item><title>Creators: The Past</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/creators-the-past/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/creators-the-past/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Creators: The Past&amp;rdquo; is an Italian science fiction fantasy film directed by Piergiuseppe Zaia, who also co-wrote the screenplay with Eleonora Fani and composed the soundtrack. The film features a notable cast, including Eleonora Fani, Jennifer Mischiati, Bruce Payne, and guest appearances by Gérard Depardieu and William Shatner. The plot revolves around the manipulation of mankind&amp;rsquo;s destiny by a race of powerful extraterrestrials known as the Creators. It was announced as the first part of a planned trilogy, with the next two installments being &amp;ldquo;Creators: The Present&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Creators: The Future.</description></item><item><title>Fingerprints of the Gods: The Evidence of Earth's Lost Civilization</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/fingerprints-of-the-gods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/fingerprints-of-the-gods/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Fingerprints of the Gods: The Evidence of Earth&amp;rsquo;s Lost Civilization&amp;rdquo; by Graham Hancock, published in 1995, explores the hypothesis of a highly advanced civilization existing in prehistory, serving as the progenitor of all known ancient civilizations. Hancock proposes that this civilization, centered around Antarctica, ended catastrophically at the end of the last ice age but passed on significant knowledge in astronomy, architecture, and mathematics. The evidence for this lost civilization, according to Hancock, is found in ancient Egypt and American civilizations like the Olmec, Aztec, and Maya.</description></item><item><title>Is Genesis History?</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/is-genesis-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/is-genesis-history/</guid><description>Is Genesis History?&amp;quot; is a 2017 American film directed by Thomas Purifoy Jr., which presents the perspective of Young Earth creationism. This form of creation science challenges established scientific facts regarding the origins of the universe, Earth, solar system, and life itself, advocating for a literal interpretation of the biblical narratives. The film posits that the Earth was created in six 24-hour days and supports the Genesis accounts of Adam and Eve, the fall, a global flood, and the Tower of Babel.</description></item><item><title>Kosmographia — The Official Randall Carlson Podcast</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/kosmographia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/kosmographia/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Kosmographia — The Official Randall Carlson Podcast&amp;rdquo; is a thought-provoking and in-depth podcast series hosted by Randall Carlson, a renowned geological and architectural theorist, teacher, and scholar. The podcast delves into a wide array of subjects that intersect science, mythology, geology, and ancient history, reflecting Carlson&amp;rsquo;s multifaceted interests and expertise.
Carlson, known for his meticulous research and comprehensive knowledge, explores theories and evidence related to Earth&amp;rsquo;s geological history, catastrophic events, and the mysteries of ancient civilizations.</description></item></channel></rss>