<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Raëlism on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/topics/ra%C3%ABlism/</link><description>Recent content in Raëlism on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/topics/ra%C3%ABlism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Extraterrestrials Took Me To Their Planet</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/extraterrestrials-took-me-to-their-planet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/extraterrestrials-took-me-to-their-planet/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Extraterrestrials Took Me to Their Planet&amp;rdquo; is a book written by Claude Vorilhon, also known as Raël, the founder of the Raëlian Movement. The book is a sequel to Raël&amp;rsquo;s first book, &amp;ldquo;The Book Which Tells the Truth,&amp;rdquo; and it expands on the ideas and teachings presented in that work. In &amp;ldquo;Extraterrestrials Took Me to Their Planet,&amp;rdquo; Raël describes his experiences with extraterrestrial beings, whom he refers to as the Elohim.</description></item><item><title>Let's Welcome The Extraterrestrials</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/lets-welcome-the-extraterrestrials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/lets-welcome-the-extraterrestrials/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s Welcome the Extraterrestrials,&amp;rdquo; the third book in the Raelian series, is a compilation of Rael&amp;rsquo;s responses to frequently asked questions post-publication of his first two books. It addresses apparent contradictions between his earlier messages, clarifies the Raelian stance on various topics, and offers insights into the beliefs and teachings of the Raelian Movement. The book delves into the origins of life on Earth, the role of the Elohim in human history, the relationship between humans and their creators, and the future of humanity in relation to extraterrestrial life.</description></item><item><title>Raelian Movement | The true origin of life on Earth: Extraterrestrials created us in their image</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/rael-dot-org/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/rael-dot-org/</guid><description>The Raelian Movement, founded in 1974, centers on the teachings of Rael, who claims to have encountered the Elohim, a group of scientists purported to have created humanity. The movement has grown to over 130,000 members across more than 120 countries. It focuses on spreading the Elohim&amp;rsquo;s message and building an embassy for them on Earth, as detailed in Rael&amp;rsquo;s teachings. This non-profit organization is funded by its members, emphasizing a vision of a world where science is paramount and violence is eradicated.</description></item><item><title>Space a Go Go (archived website)</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/space-a-gogo-dot-com/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/resources/space-a-gogo-dot-com/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Space a Go Go&amp;rdquo; is a website that presents the theory that humans were created by extraterrestrials, drawing on archaeological evidence and interpretations of ancient texts. It suggests that UFOs are piloted by extraterrestrials who have been trying to make their existence known to humanity. The site references the work of Zecharia Sitchin, who claimed that ancient clay tablets from Iraq recorded the creation of humans by extraterrestrials. It also mentions geneticists questioning the natural evolution theory, suggesting that human genetic code indicates an extraterrestrial author.</description></item></channel></rss>