<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Spirituality on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/topics/spirituality/</link><description>Recent content in Spirituality on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/topics/spirituality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Book of Mormon</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-mormon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/book-of-mormon/</guid><description>The Book of Mormon, foundational to the Latter Day Saint movement, is a religious text published by Joseph Smith in 1830. Smith described it as a translation of golden plates shown to him by an angel, Moroni. The narrative details the history of ancient peoples in the Americas, focusing on their spiritual journey and teachings, with a pivotal event being the appearance of Jesus Christ post-resurrection. It&amp;rsquo;s considered by adherents as a complementary scripture to the Bible, offering insights into Christian theology and moral teachings.</description></item><item><title>Divine Signposts</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/divine-signposts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/divine-signposts/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Divine Signposts&amp;rdquo; (大本, Ōmoto) by Onisaburo Deguchi (出口王仁三郎) is a foundational text in the spiritual and religious tradition of Ōmoto (大本), a Japanese new religious movement. Written in 1904 when Onisaburo was 33 years old, this work is one of his earliest writings and consists of 14 volumes. It lays out the basis of Ōmoto&amp;rsquo;s teachings, emphasizing the essence of faith and Onisaburo&amp;rsquo;s mission of world salvation.
This sacred text is intended to be read by Ōmoto believers as a part of their daily spiritual practice, serving as both a doctrinal book and a guide to true faith.</description></item><item><title>Internet Sacred Text Archive</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/internet-sacred-text-archive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/internet-sacred-text-archive/</guid><description>The Internet Sacred Text Archive (ISTA), founded by John Bruno Hare in 1999 in Santa Cruz, California, is a website dedicated to preserving electronic public domain religious texts. Hare, a software engineer, initiated this project from his home as an intellectual challenge, digitizing over 1,000 public domain books on religion, folklore, and mythology to promote religious tolerance through knowledge. The archive&amp;rsquo;s texts are divided into 77 categories, and its maintenance costs are supported by sales of the website&amp;rsquo;s content on DVDs, CDs, or USB flash drives.</description></item><item><title>Kitáb-i-Aqdas</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/kitab-i-aqdas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/kitab-i-aqdas/</guid><description>The Kitáb-i-Aqdas, known as &amp;ldquo;The Most Holy Book,&amp;rdquo; is the central book of the Bahá&amp;rsquo;í Faith, written by Bahá’u’lláh, the founder of the faith. Composed in the 19th century, this sacred text lays down the laws, principles, and institutions for the Bahá&amp;rsquo;í community, and is considered the charter for a future global civilization.
The Kitáb-i-Aqdas not only provides laws and ordinances for the spiritual and daily life of believers but also articulates the administrative principles and structures of the Bahá&amp;rsquo;í Faith.</description></item><item><title>Terranigma</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/terranigma/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/terranigma/</guid><description>Terranigma, developed by Quintet (株式会社クインテット) and published by Enix for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System (SNES), is a 1995 action role-playing game with a rich narrative and thematic depth. The game&amp;rsquo;s story centers around Ark, a mischievous teenager from the underground village of Crysta. Ark&amp;rsquo;s journey begins when his curiosity triggers a series of events leading to the resurrection of life on a previously barren Earth.
The game unfolds across four main chapters.</description></item><item><title>The Collection of Divine Messages of the Cao Đài Religion of God</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/the-collection-of-divine-messages-of-cai-dai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/the-collection-of-divine-messages-of-cai-dai/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The Collection of Divine Messages&amp;rdquo; (Thánh Ngôn Hiệp Tuyển), a key scripture of the Đạo Cao Đài religion, was compiled in 1926, encapsulating the divine teachings and revelations central to this Vietnamese religious movement. This collection is comprised of two volumes of messages, believed to be communicated by the Supreme Being and various Divine Spirits to the followers of Đạo Cao Đài.
The first volume contains several critical teachings. These include the Divine Teaching of the Jade Emperor, who introduces himself and announces the names of the twelve disciples, marking a significant moment in the development of the faith​.</description></item></channel></rss>