<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Current affairs on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/topics/current-affairs/</link><description>Recent content in Current affairs on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/topics/current-affairs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Engagement</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/the-engagement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/the-engagement/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The Engagement&amp;rdquo; is a proposal addressing the Israeli-Palestinian conflict. It suggests that the conflict in the Holy Land, primarily between Jewish and Palestinian communities, represents a clash of civilizations rooted in a deep and intensive encounter between Western (Judeo-Christian) and Middle Eastern (Arab-Muslim) cultures. The proposal argues that about 80-90% of Palestinians are descendants of the People of Israel, who remained in the country after the destruction of the Second Jewish Temple and were forced to convert to Islam.</description></item><item><title>The Sky People</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/the-sky-people/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/the-sky-people/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The Sky People&amp;rdquo; by Brinsley Le Poer Trench offers a unique interpretation of human history and extraterrestrial involvement. Trench, in his book, argues that significant Biblical figures, including Adam and Eve and Noah, were originally residents of Mars. He bases this theory on what he perceives as inconsistencies between the Biblical description of the Garden of Eden and earthly environments, suggesting that the Garden of Eden was actually located on Mars, supported by his mention of canals on Mars.</description></item></channel></rss>