<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Энциклопедия on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/wiki/encyclopedia/</link><description>Recent content in Энциклопедия on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/wiki/encyclopedia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Бесконечность</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/wiki/%D0%B1%D0%B5%D1%81%D0%BA%D0%BE%D0%BD%D0%B5%D1%87%D0%BD%D0%BE%D1%81%D1%82%D1%8C/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/wiki/%D0%B1%D0%B5%D1%81%D0%BA%D0%BE%D0%BD%D0%B5%D1%87%D0%BD%D0%BE%D1%81%D1%82%D1%8C/</guid><description>Infinity in space # The concept of an infinite universe in space is based on the idea that there is no edge or boundary to the universe, and that it extends forever in all directions. This idea is supported by the observed uniformity and homogeneity of the cosmic microwave background radiation, which suggests that the universe is isotropic (the same in all directions) and homogeneous (the same at all points).</description></item><item><title>Библия</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/wiki/%D0%B1%D0%B8%D0%B1%D0%BB%D0%B8%D1%8F/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/wiki/%D0%B1%D0%B8%D0%B1%D0%BB%D0%B8%D1%8F/</guid><description>The Bible is an anthology of religious texts, written and assembled over many centuries, regarded as sacred in Jewish, Christian, and, to some extent, Islamic traditions. Its significance cannot be understated; it has shaped civilizations, informed legal systems, influenced literature and art, and guided the spiritual lives of billions of people worldwide. However, it isn&amp;rsquo;t a single book authored by one individual. Instead, the Bible is a complex library of texts, encompassing a wide range of literary genres - histories, prophecies, poetry, wisdom literature, letters, and apocalyptic writings.</description></item><item><title>Война элохимов</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/wiki/%D0%B2%D0%BE%D0%B9%D0%BD%D0%B0-%D1%8D%D0%BB%D0%BE%D1%85%D0%B8%D0%BC%D0%BE%D0%B2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/wiki/%D0%B2%D0%BE%D0%B9%D0%BD%D0%B0-%D1%8D%D0%BB%D0%BE%D1%85%D0%B8%D0%BC%D0%BE%D0%B2/</guid><description>See also # Wiki › Adamite struggle Wiki › Elohim Wiki › Lucifer Wiki › Leviathan Wiki › Serpentine rebellion Wiki › Yahweh Read more # Intro › Timeline › Age of Leo External links # Chaos (cosmogony) # Chaoskampf | Wikipedia Theomachy | Wikipedia</description></item><item><title>Всемирная эпоха</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/wiki/%D0%B2%D1%81%D0%B5%D0%BC%D0%B8%D1%80%D0%BD%D0%B0%D1%8F-%D1%8D%D0%BF%D0%BE%D1%85%D0%B0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/wiki/%D0%B2%D1%81%D0%B5%D0%BC%D0%B8%D1%80%D0%BD%D0%B0%D1%8F-%D1%8D%D0%BF%D0%BE%D1%85%D0%B0/</guid><description>The precessional Great Year is a term is used to describe the approximately 26'000 year cycle of the slow wobble of the Earth&amp;rsquo;s axis. This cycle of precession affects the position of the stars in the sky and the way that the sun appears to move through the constellations over time.
In astrology, the precessional World Ages are often associated with different historical periods and cultural developments, with each Age being seen as having a distinct spiritual or cultural significance.</description></item><item><title>Генная инженерия</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/wiki/%D0%B3%D0%B5%D0%BD%D0%BD%D0%B0%D1%8F-%D0%B8%D0%BD%D0%B6%D0%B5%D0%BD%D0%B5%D1%80%D0%B8%D1%8F/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/wiki/%D0%B3%D0%B5%D0%BD%D0%BD%D0%B0%D1%8F-%D0%B8%D0%BD%D0%B6%D0%B5%D0%BD%D0%B5%D1%80%D0%B8%D1%8F/</guid><description>See also # Wiki › Genesis Wiki › Life engineering Wiki › Synthetic biology Wiki › Synthetic genomics External links # Genetic engineering | Wikipedia</description></item><item><title>Древние строители</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/wiki/%D0%B4%D1%80%D0%B5%D0%B2%D0%BD%D0%B8%D0%B5-%D1%81%D1%82%D1%80%D0%BE%D0%B8%D1%82%D0%B5%D0%BB%D0%B8/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/wiki/%D0%B4%D1%80%D0%B5%D0%B2%D0%BD%D0%B8%D0%B5-%D1%81%D1%82%D1%80%D0%BE%D0%B8%D1%82%D0%B5%D0%BB%D0%B8/</guid><description>Ancient Builders typically refers to the architects, engineers, and skilled workers who created structures, such as buildings, temples, pyramids, and other monumental structures, in ancient civilizations. These ancient builders used a variety of materials and techniques, depending on the resources and technological abilities available to them. They often incorporated elements of sacred geometry, religious beliefs, and cultural symbols into their structures, which were sometimes used for religious or political purposes.</description></item><item><title>Инженерия жизни</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/wiki/%D0%B8%D0%BD%D0%B6%D0%B5%D0%BD%D0%B5%D1%80%D0%B8%D1%8F-%D0%B6%D0%B8%D0%B7%D0%BD%D0%B8/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/wiki/%D0%B8%D0%BD%D0%B6%D0%B5%D0%BD%D0%B5%D1%80%D0%B8%D1%8F-%D0%B6%D0%B8%D0%B7%D0%BD%D0%B8/</guid><description>See also # Wiki › Genesis Wiki › Genetic engineering Wiki › Synthetic biology Wiki › Synthetic genomics External links #</description></item><item><title>Космические силы США</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/wiki/%D0%BA%D0%BE%D1%81%D0%BC%D0%B8%D1%87%D0%B5%D1%81%D0%BA%D0%B8%D0%B5-%D1%81%D0%B8%D0%BB%D1%8B-%D1%81%D1%88%D0%B0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/wiki/%D0%BA%D0%BE%D1%81%D0%BC%D0%B8%D1%87%D0%B5%D1%81%D0%BA%D0%B8%D0%B5-%D1%81%D0%B8%D0%BB%D1%8B-%D1%81%D1%88%D0%B0/</guid><description>The United States Space Force (USSF), established on December 20, 2019, represents the sixth branch of the U.S. Armed Forces. Originally proposed by the Trump administration, the Space Force is a distinct and independent military service under the Department of the Air Force, alongside the U.S. Air Force. This article explores the origins, development, and strategic importance of the USSF, highlighting how President Trump perceived the necessity of military capabilities in space.</description></item><item><title>Левиафан</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/wiki/%D0%BB%D0%B5%D0%B2%D0%B8%D0%B0%D1%84%D0%B0%D0%BD/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/wiki/%D0%BB%D0%B5%D0%B2%D0%B8%D0%B0%D1%84%D0%B0%D0%BD/</guid><description>The Leviathan is a mythical sea monster mentioned in the Bible, specifically in the book of Job and in the book of Psalms. In the Bible, the Leviathan is described as a powerful and fearsome creature that lives in the sea and is difficult to control.
The Leviathan has been interpreted in various ways throughout history. In some interpretations, it is seen as a symbol of chaos and evil, while in others it is viewed as a symbol of the power of God and the natural order of the universe.</description></item><item><title>Масс-эффект</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/wiki/%D0%BC%D0%B0%D1%81%D1%81-%D1%8D%D1%84%D1%84%D0%B5%D0%BA%D1%82/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/wiki/%D0%BC%D0%B0%D1%81%D1%81-%D1%8D%D1%84%D1%84%D0%B5%D0%BA%D1%82/</guid><description>Law of masstime # The law of masstime simply states that time is inversely proportional to mass.
This effect of mass, or simply mass effect, or the law of physics where time is inversely proportional to the mass or level of form of life, is a universal law that can be observed empirically in a wide range of kinetic bodies, particularly in life forms. For example, a eukaryotic cell exhibits a higher degree of gesticulations in a given period of time relative to its body size compared to an ant, which, in turn, generates more kinetic activity than an elephant.</description></item></channel></rss>