<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference work on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/topics/reference-work/</link><description>Recent content in Reference work on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/topics/reference-work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sefaria: A Living Library of Torah</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/sefaria/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/sefaria/</guid><description>Sefaria, founded in 2011 by journalist Joshua Foer and Brett Lockspeiser, a former product manager at Google, is a remarkable digital library of Jewish texts. Its name, derived from the Hebrew words &amp;ldquo;sefer&amp;rdquo; (book) and &amp;ldquo;sifria&amp;rdquo; (library), encapsulates its mission to be a comprehensive, accessible repository of Jewish knowledge​​​​.
The platform is designed as an open-source, free-content digital library, offering a wide array of Jewish texts in original languages like Hebrew, Aramaic, and Judeo-Arabic, along with translations.</description></item><item><title>The Zohar: Pritzker Edition</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/the-zohar-pritzker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/the-zohar-pritzker/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The Zohar: Pritzker Edition&amp;rdquo; by Daniel Matt is a monumental translation of the Zohar, the foundational work of Jewish mysticism. This 12-volume series is the first to be translated from a critical Aramaic text, based on original manuscripts. Matt&amp;rsquo;s extensive commentary clarifies Kabbalistic symbolism and terminology, citing sources from biblical, rabbinic, and kabbalistic texts. Acclaimed for its poetic language and insightful exegesis, the translation makes the complex Zohar accessible to a wider audience, both scholarly and general.</description></item><item><title>Wonders in the Sky: Unexplained Aerial Objects from Antiquity to Modern Times</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/wonders-in-the-sky/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/wonders-in-the-sky/</guid><description>Wonders in the Sky: Unexplained Aerial Objects from Antiquity to Modern Times&amp;quot; by Jacques Vallée and Chris Aubeck is a comprehensive investigation into the history of unidentified flying objects (UFOs). The book examines over 500 reports of UFO sightings from ancient times up to the year 1879, a period before the profound changes brought by the Industrial Revolution and the advent of modern aircraft like airplanes and dirigibles.
The work is noted for its rigorous approach to paranormal investigation, presenting a detailed compendium of pre-twentieth-century UFO accounts.</description></item></channel></rss>