<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>History of Science on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/topics/history-of-science/</link><description>Recent content in History of Science on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/topics/history-of-science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alternative History VS Mainstream History or War on Facts</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/alternative-history-s-mainstream-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/alternative-history-s-mainstream-history/</guid><description>The video &amp;ldquo;Alternative History VS Mainstream History or War on Facts&amp;rdquo; made by Versadoco delves into the complexities of scientific paradigms in the context of historical studies. It discusses how these paradigms, often linked to career advancements, can make it challenging for archaeologists to question dominant perspectives. The evolving nature of science, seen not as a dogma but as an instrument to understand reality, plays a critical role in shaping our understanding of history, which itself is fragmented and open to interpretation.</description></item><item><title>Hamlet's Mill: An Essay Investigating the Origins of Human Knowledge and Its Transmission Through Myth</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/hamlets-mill/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/hamlets-mill/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Hamlet&amp;rsquo;s Mill: An Essay Investigating the Origins of Human Knowledge and Its Transmission Through Myth,&amp;rdquo; written by Giorgio de Santillana and Hertha von Dechend, presents the argument that ancient mythologies contain sophisticated knowledge of the precession of the equinoxes. This knowledge, they argue, indicates a Neolithic discovery and a long-lived Megalithic civilization of remarkable sophistication, particularly in astronomical observation. The authors suggest that this civilization&amp;rsquo;s knowledge was encoded in myths, often represented by a millstone and a young protagonist, which they interpret primarily through the lens of archaeoastronomy.</description></item><item><title>Is Genesis History?</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/is-genesis-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/is-genesis-history/</guid><description>Is Genesis History?&amp;quot; is a 2017 American film directed by Thomas Purifoy Jr., which presents the perspective of Young Earth creationism. This form of creation science challenges established scientific facts regarding the origins of the universe, Earth, solar system, and life itself, advocating for a literal interpretation of the biblical narratives. The film posits that the Earth was created in six 24-hour days and supports the Genesis accounts of Adam and Eve, the fall, a global flood, and the Tower of Babel.</description></item><item><title>Kosmographia — The Official Randall Carlson Podcast</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/kosmographia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/kosmographia/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Kosmographia — The Official Randall Carlson Podcast&amp;rdquo; is a thought-provoking and in-depth podcast series hosted by Randall Carlson, a renowned geological and architectural theorist, teacher, and scholar. The podcast delves into a wide array of subjects that intersect science, mythology, geology, and ancient history, reflecting Carlson&amp;rsquo;s multifaceted interests and expertise.
Carlson, known for his meticulous research and comprehensive knowledge, explores theories and evidence related to Earth&amp;rsquo;s geological history, catastrophic events, and the mysteries of ancient civilizations.</description></item><item><title>Science After Babel</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/science-after-babel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/science-after-babel/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Science After Babel&amp;rdquo; by David Berlinski is a book that challenges the established norms and widely accepted theories in contemporary science. Berlinski, known for his deep learning, close reasoning, and sharp wit, critiques what he considers to be the shibboleths of modern science. These include widely accepted concepts in Darwinism, reductionism, the Standard Model of particle physics, and the idea of &amp;ldquo;talking&amp;rdquo; chimpanzees.
In his book, Berlinski questions the solidity of what is often passed off as secure scientific knowledge.</description></item><item><title>The Devil's Delusion: Atheism and Its Scientific Pretension</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/the-devils-delusion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/the-devils-delusion/</guid><description>In &amp;ldquo;The Devil&amp;rsquo;s Delusion: Atheism and Its Scientific Pretensions,&amp;rdquo; David Berlinski mounts a vigorous critique of scientific atheism, particularly addressing the assertions made by figures like Richard Dawkins and Sam Harris. Berlinski, a secular Jew and mathematician, questions the completeness and authority of science in answering profound existential and moral questions.
Berlinski argues that the science often cited by atheists to debunk religious beliefs actually does not conclusively negate the possibility of a divine existence.</description></item></channel></rss>