<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>behind-the-scenes on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/categories/behind-the-scenes/</link><description>Recent content in behind-the-scenes on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/categories/behind-the-scenes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Roadmap after first year since launch</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/articles/roadmap-after-first-year-since-launch/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/articles/roadmap-after-first-year-since-launch/</guid><description>👉 Disclaimer: This is a English-only article. The inception of this website traces back to last year&amp;rsquo;s autumn equinox. I was perched in a rooftop bar in Jerusalem, with the Old City stretching out before me in the east. From that moment to now, the content has burgeoned remarkably. I&amp;rsquo;ve dedicated considerable effort to refining the user experience of the site, and the wiki has been meticulously curated, almost to the limits of what a single maintainer can achieve.</description></item><item><title>Content log 03/23 🪵</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/articles/content-log-03/23/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/articles/content-log-03/23/</guid><description>It has been six months since we launched the Wheel of Heaven Knowledge Base website, and it has been a lot of work ever since. As the primary content creator for the site, I thought it would be helpful to start a content log to recapitulate what has happened and what I have been working on during this time.
In terms of website traffic, we have seen a steady increase since the launch, but the web site has been mostly off the radar for many as of yet.</description></item><item><title>Hello World! 👋</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/articles/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/articles/hello-world/</guid><description>Hello World! Wheel of Heaven has been launched offically! Wheel of Heaven is a knowledge base exploring the working hypothesis that life on Earth was intelligently designed by an extraterrestrial civilization, the so-called Elohim.
While the working hypothesis is not necessarily something new and there are a certain number of forethinkers within the realm of ancient astronauts, creationism and/or an neo-euhemeristic reading of ancient mythology, the foundation upon which the premises are residing is an unapologetic re-interpretation Raëlism, a new religious movement that goes back to a Frenchman that avowedly met the representative of an extraterrestrial civilization, Yahweh, that left us with an important message of very deep philsophical implications if proven true.</description></item></channel></rss>