<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>百科事典 on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/wiki/encyclopedia/</link><description>Recent content in 百科事典 on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/wiki/encyclopedia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>tl;dr</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/wiki/tldr/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/wiki/tldr/</guid><description>「tl;dr」はインターネット文化から生まれ、特にフォーラム、ソーシャルメディア、ディスカッションボードなどのオンラインコミュニティで人気を得ました。これは、一部のユーザーが煩雑で時間のかかると感じる長い投稿や記事に対する応答として生まれました。
「tl;dr」という略語は、「too long; didn&amp;rsquo;t read」（長すぎるので読まなかった）を意味します。長いコンテンツへの関心の欠如を簡潔に表現する方法であり、また要約のリクエストとしても使用されます。誰かがメッセージに「tl;dr」を含めるとき、基本的には「このテキストは私にとって長すぎるので、短いバージョンを提供してください」と言っていることになります。
「tl;dr」の正確な起源は明確には分かっていませんが、それは2000年代初頭にオンラインコミュニティ内で生まれたと考えられています。その使用法は広まり、最初の目的を超えてユーモラスなものや皮肉な意味合いも含むようになりました。長い情報を簡潔に要約したり無視したりするためによく使われる一般的な略語となっています。
外部リンク # TL;DR | Wikipedia</description></item><item><title>UFO学</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/wiki/ufo%E5%AD%A6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/wiki/ufo%E5%AD%A6/</guid><description>See also # Wiki › Ancient Astronaut hypothesis External links # Ufology | Wikipedia List of ufologists | Wikipedia List of reported UFO sightings | Wikipedia</description></item><item><title>Wheel of Heaven</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/wiki/wheel-of-heaven/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/wiki/wheel-of-heaven/</guid><description>Working hypothesis # A working hypothesis is a specific type of hypothesis, namely one that is provisionally accepted as a basis for further research in the hope that a tenable theory will be produced, even if the hypothesis ultimately fails. In this way, a working hypothesis is an accepted starting point for further research. A hypothesis in turn is simply put a supposition or proposed explanation made on the basis of limited evidence as a starting point for further investigation.</description></item><item><title>アダマイト</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/wiki/%E3%82%A2%E3%83%80%E3%83%9E%E3%82%A4%E3%83%88/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/wiki/%E3%82%A2%E3%83%80%E3%83%9E%E3%82%A4%E3%83%88/</guid><description>This article explores the history and mythology of the Adamites, a unique group believed to have existed during the time of the Garden of Eden. They should not be confused with the sect of early Christian Adamites who were active during the 2nd to 4th centuries CE. Despite sharing the same name, the two groups are entirely unrelated. The Adamites discussed in this article are described in certain interpretations of ancient scriptures as having participated in a union with a rebellious faction of the Elohim known as the Serpent, resulting in a hybrid offspring.</description></item><item><title>アダマイトの闘争</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/wiki/%E3%82%A2%E3%83%80%E3%83%9E%E3%82%A4%E3%83%88%E3%81%AE%E9%97%98%E4%BA%89/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/wiki/%E3%82%A2%E3%83%80%E3%83%9E%E3%82%A4%E3%83%88%E3%81%AE%E9%97%98%E4%BA%89/</guid><description>Sequence of events # The Adamite Struggle refers an to epoch-spanning struggle that started in the Age of Leo, which delineates the course of humanity&amp;rsquo;s evolution from their creation to their eventual emergence as independent and autonomous entities. This narrative presents the perspective of the human Adamites, who were embroiled in a complex political struggle against their creators, the Elohim.
The Adamites, also referred to as early human beings in Eden, were created by Elohimite scientists on Earth.</description></item><item><title>アダムとイヴ</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/wiki/%E3%82%A2%E3%83%80%E3%83%A0%E3%81%A8%E3%82%A4%E3%83%B4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/wiki/%E3%82%A2%E3%83%80%E3%83%A0%E3%81%A8%E3%82%A4%E3%83%B4/</guid><description>Adam and Eve are the first man and woman according to the creation story in the Bible&amp;rsquo;s book of Genesis. They are considered the first human beings created by God, and are believed to have lived in the Garden of Eden before disobeying God&amp;rsquo;s command and being expelled from the garden (Genesis 3). Adam is described as the first man created by God from the dust of the ground, while Eve is described as the first woman, created from one of Adam&amp;rsquo;s ribs (Genesis 2:7, 2:22).</description></item><item><title>アブラハム</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/wiki/%E3%82%A2%E3%83%96%E3%83%A9%E3%83%8F%E3%83%A0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/wiki/%E3%82%A2%E3%83%96%E3%83%A9%E3%83%8F%E3%83%A0/</guid><description>Abraham is a central figure in Judaism, Christianity, and Islam and is considered the father of these three monotheistic religions. In the Bible, he is described as the father of Isaac and a patriarch of the Israelites. In the Tanakh, he is considered the first Hebrew and the founder of the Jewish nation. In the Quran, Abraham is considered a prophet of Allah and a friend of God.
In the Bible, Abraham is described as:</description></item><item><title>アメリカ宇宙軍</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/wiki/%E3%82%A2%E3%83%A1%E3%83%AA%E3%82%AB%E5%AE%87%E5%AE%99%E8%BB%8D/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/wiki/%E3%82%A2%E3%83%A1%E3%83%AA%E3%82%AB%E5%AE%87%E5%AE%99%E8%BB%8D/</guid><description>The United States Space Force (USSF), established on December 20, 2019, represents the sixth branch of the U.S. Armed Forces. Originally proposed by the Trump administration, the Space Force is a distinct and independent military service under the Department of the Air Force, alongside the U.S. Air Force. This article explores the origins, development, and strategic importance of the USSF, highlighting how President Trump perceived the necessity of military capabilities in space.</description></item><item><title>イエス</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/wiki/%E3%82%A4%E3%82%A8%E3%82%B9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/wiki/%E3%82%A4%E3%82%A8%E3%82%B9/</guid><description>Jesus, also known as Jesus of Nazareth or Jesus Christ, is the central figure of Christianity and one of the most important figures in world history. According to Christian belief, Jesus was born in Bethlehem in Judea in the 1st century BC and was crucified in Jerusalem by the Romans around 30 AD.
Jesus is considered by Christians to be the Son of God and the Messiah (or savior) prophesied in the Old Testament.</description></item><item><title>ミーム</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/wiki/%E3%83%9F%E3%83%BC%E3%83%A0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ja/wiki/%E3%83%9F%E3%83%BC%E3%83%A0/</guid><description>A mytheme is a basic unit or component of a myth, folklore, or religious tradition. It refers to a recurring motif, symbol, story, or character that appears in multiple myths and legends across cultures and time periods. Mythemes often serve as building blocks for larger myths and stories and can convey important cultural values, beliefs, or moral lessons. In comparative mythology, the study of mythemes helps scholars identify common themes, symbols, and motifs across cultures and understand how they are transformed and evolve over time.</description></item></channel></rss>