<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Archive on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/topics/archive/</link><description>Recent content in Archive on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/topics/archive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bahaipedia</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/bahaipedia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/bahaipedia/</guid><description>Bahaipedia is an independent, collaboratively edited encyclopedia focused on the Bahá&amp;rsquo;í Faith. Initiated in March 2007 by David Haslip, it aims to connect readers with primary source materials foundational to Bahá&amp;rsquo;í teachings and history. The site, powered by MediaWiki, features over 18,481 pages, edited by volunteers from diverse backgrounds. Bahaipedia includes sister projects like Bahaimedia for media storage, Bahaiworks for historical documents, and Bahai9.com for quotes and resources. The primary server is in Virginia, with secondary servers globally.</description></item><item><title>Internet Sacred Text Archive</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/internet-sacred-text-archive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/internet-sacred-text-archive/</guid><description>The Internet Sacred Text Archive (ISTA), founded by John Bruno Hare in 1999 in Santa Cruz, California, is a website dedicated to preserving electronic public domain religious texts. Hare, a software engineer, initiated this project from his home as an intellectual challenge, digitizing over 1,000 public domain books on religion, folklore, and mythology to promote religious tolerance through knowledge. The archive&amp;rsquo;s texts are divided into 77 categories, and its maintenance costs are supported by sales of the website&amp;rsquo;s content on DVDs, CDs, or USB flash drives.</description></item><item><title>Temporary Temples</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/temporary-temples/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/temporary-temples/</guid><description>The website Temporary Temples is dedicated to exploring and documenting crop circles, particularly in the UK. It provides information about the latest crop circle formations, including their locations, images, and descriptions. Additionally, the site features galleries showcasing various crop circle designs throughout the years. It offers insights into their patterns, sizes, and intricacies. The website also provides information about events, tours, and workshops related to crop circles for those interested in engaging more deeply with the phenomenon.</description></item><item><title>The Church of Jesus of Latter-Day Saints: Scriptures</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/the-church-of-jesus-latter-day-saints-scriptures/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/the-church-of-jesus-latter-day-saints-scriptures/</guid><description>The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints&amp;rsquo; Scriptures resource offers a comprehensive collection of religious texts central to the faith, including the Old Testament, New Testament, Book of Mormon, Doctrine and Covenants, Pearl of Great Price, and various study aids and proclamations. The history of these scriptures reveals a dynamic process of compilation, revision, and enhancement to make these sacred texts accessible and relevant to its members.
Key milestones in the history of these scriptures include the commissioning of the King James Version of the Bible by King James I, the translation and subsequent revisions of the Book of Mormon initiated by Joseph Smith, and the compilation of Joseph Smith&amp;rsquo;s revelations into the Book of Commandments, which later evolved into the Doctrine and Covenants​.</description></item><item><title>The Electronic Text Corpus of Sumerian Literature</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/the-electronic-text-corpus-of-sumerian-literature/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/the-electronic-text-corpus-of-sumerian-literature/</guid><description>The Electronic Text Corpus of Sumerian Literature (ETCSL), in its second edition, is a comprehensive digital project aimed at compiling, translating, and publishing the extensive body of Sumerian literature. This literature, dating back to around 2500 BCE, includes a vast array of poetic forms such as hymns, laments, prayers, fables, and proverbs, largely reconstructed from thousands of fragmented clay tablets inscribed in cuneiform.
The ETCSL project, initiated as a pilot in 1997 with funding from the University of Oxford, aimed to establish the corpus&amp;rsquo;s extent and develop technical publication procedures.</description></item></channel></rss>