<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cinematographic-film on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/medium/cinematographic-film/</link><description>Recent content in cinematographic-film on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/medium/cinematographic-film/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Creators: The Past</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/creators-the-past/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/creators-the-past/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Creators: The Past&amp;rdquo; is an Italian science fiction fantasy film directed by Piergiuseppe Zaia, who also co-wrote the screenplay with Eleonora Fani and composed the soundtrack. The film features a notable cast, including Eleonora Fani, Jennifer Mischiati, Bruce Payne, and guest appearances by Gérard Depardieu and William Shatner. The plot revolves around the manipulation of mankind&amp;rsquo;s destiny by a race of powerful extraterrestrials known as the Creators. It was announced as the first part of a planned trilogy, with the next two installments being &amp;ldquo;Creators: The Present&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Creators: The Future.</description></item><item><title>Hard to Be a God</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/hard-to-be-a-god/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/hard-to-be-a-god/</guid><description>Hard to Be a God (1989) is a West German-Soviet-French-Swiss science fiction film directed by Peter Fleischmann, based on the novel of the same name by Arkady and Boris Strugatsky. The film is set on a distant planet that mirrors Earth&amp;rsquo;s Middle Ages, where society has not progressed beyond a primitive, feudal state. This alien world is being observed by Earth scientists posing as noble feudal lords.
The central character, Anton, is one of the scientists sent from Earth.</description></item><item><title>Jurassic World</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/jurassic-world/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/es/resources/jurassic-world/</guid><description>Jurassic World is a 2015 American science fiction adventure film and the fourth installment in the Jurassic Park franchise. Directed by Colin Trevorrow and written by Trevorrow, Derek Connolly, Rick Jaffa, and Amanda Silver, the film is set 22 years after the events of the original Jurassic Park and takes place on the same fictional Central American island of Isla Nublar, off Costa Rica&amp;rsquo;s Pacific Coast.
In Jurassic World, the island has been transformed into a fully functioning dinosaur theme park, as originally envisioned by John Hammond.</description></item></channel></rss>