<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mythology on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/topics/mythology/</link><description>Recent content in Mythology on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/topics/mythology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Epic of Gilgamesh</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/epic-of-gilgamesh/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/epic-of-gilgamesh/</guid><description>The Epic of Gilgamesh is an ancient Mesopotamian poem, regarded as one of the earliest great works of literature. It narrates the adventures of Gilgamesh, the historical king of Uruk, and his quest for immortality, exploring themes of friendship, the human condition, and the fear of death. The epic, written in cuneiform on clay tablets, dates back to the early 3rd millennium BCE.
The story begins with the introduction of Gilgamesh, two-thirds god and one-third human, who is a tyrannical king of Uruk.</description></item><item><title>Internet Sacred Text Archive</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/internet-sacred-text-archive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/internet-sacred-text-archive/</guid><description>The Internet Sacred Text Archive (ISTA), founded by John Bruno Hare in 1999 in Santa Cruz, California, is a website dedicated to preserving electronic public domain religious texts. Hare, a software engineer, initiated this project from his home as an intellectual challenge, digitizing over 1,000 public domain books on religion, folklore, and mythology to promote religious tolerance through knowledge. The archive&amp;rsquo;s texts are divided into 77 categories, and its maintenance costs are supported by sales of the website&amp;rsquo;s content on DVDs, CDs, or USB flash drives.</description></item><item><title>Mazzaroth | The Alpha and the Omega</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/mazzaroth-dot-com/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/mazzaroth-dot-com/</guid><description>Jim A. Cornwell&amp;rsquo;s website, mazzaroth.com, offers a detailed exploration of the interplay between the zodiac, biblical narratives, and ancient civilizations. It delves into the correlations of zodiac symbols with biblical patriarchs, interprets the creation story in Genesis in relation to astronomical events, and examines the historical and astronomical connections to various periods, such as the Bronze Age and Egyptian Dynasties. The site also explores themes like the New Age, the Antichrist, and biblical prophecies of tribulation, linking these concepts to astronomical interpretations and the concept of completeness symbolized by the number twelve.</description></item><item><title>Mazzaroth; or, The constellations</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/mazzaroth-rolleston/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/mazzaroth-rolleston/</guid><description>Frances Rolleston&amp;rsquo;s book, &amp;ldquo;Mazzaroth; or, The Constellations,&amp;rdquo; explores the significance and symbolism of the constellations in the context of divine revelation and biblical prophecy. She contends that the constellations hold a deeper, spiritual meaning that has been obscured by associations with pagan mythology and a lack of understanding of their original intent.
Rolleston argues that the constellations and their names, which are known worldwide and throughout history, point to a common origin both for humanity and these celestial symbols.</description></item><item><title>The Gospel in the Stars</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/the-gospels-in-the-stars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/the-gospels-in-the-stars/</guid><description>Joseph A. Seiss&amp;rsquo; book &amp;ldquo;The Gospel in the Stars&amp;rdquo; presents a unique interpretation of the constellations, suggesting that they carry a divine message relating to the gospel of Jesus Christ. Seiss, an American pastor and author, proposes that the arrangement and symbolism of the constellations have been used throughout human history as a means to convey knowledge and wisdom, particularly concerning the nature of God and the plan of salvation.</description></item><item><title>The Pillar of Enoch</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/pillar-of-enoch-dot-com/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/pillar-of-enoch-dot-com/</guid><description>Helena Lehman&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Pillar of Enoch&amp;rdquo; website is a resource for those interested in Judeo-Christian spiritual truths, ancient history, and future prophecies related to signs in the heavens as connected to Bible prophecy. The site features her &amp;ldquo;Language of God Book Series,&amp;rdquo; which explores biblical allegory and symbolism. The series delves into the prophetic imagery of the Bible, sacred monuments like the Great Pyramid and Solomon&amp;rsquo;s Temple, and connections to constellations like Orion.</description></item><item><title>Wonders in the Sky: Unexplained Aerial Objects from Antiquity to Modern Times</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/wonders-in-the-sky/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/resources/wonders-in-the-sky/</guid><description>Wonders in the Sky: Unexplained Aerial Objects from Antiquity to Modern Times&amp;quot; by Jacques Vallée and Chris Aubeck is a comprehensive investigation into the history of unidentified flying objects (UFOs). The book examines over 500 reports of UFO sightings from ancient times up to the year 1879, a period before the profound changes brought by the Industrial Revolution and the advent of modern aircraft like airplanes and dirigibles.
The work is noted for its rigorous approach to paranormal investigation, presenting a detailed compendium of pre-twentieth-century UFO accounts.</description></item></channel></rss>