<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Encyclopédie on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/wiki/encyclopedia/</link><description>Recent content in Encyclopédie on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/wiki/encyclopedia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Abraham</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/wiki/abraham/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/wiki/abraham/</guid><description>Abraham is a central figure in Judaism, Christianity, and Islam and is considered the father of these three monotheistic religions. In the Bible, he is described as the father of Isaac and a patriarch of the Israelites. In the Tanakh, he is considered the first Hebrew and the founder of the Jewish nation. In the Quran, Abraham is considered a prophet of Allah and a friend of God.
In the Bible, Abraham is described as:</description></item><item><title>Adam et Ève</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/wiki/adam-et-%C3%A8ve/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/wiki/adam-et-%C3%A8ve/</guid><description>Adam and Eve are the first man and woman according to the creation story in the Bible&amp;rsquo;s book of Genesis. They are considered the first human beings created by God, and are believed to have lived in the Garden of Eden before disobeying God&amp;rsquo;s command and being expelled from the garden (Genesis 3). Adam is described as the first man created by God from the dust of the ground, while Eve is described as the first woman, created from one of Adam&amp;rsquo;s ribs (Genesis 2:7, 2:22).</description></item><item><title>Adamites</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/wiki/adamites/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/wiki/adamites/</guid><description>This article explores the history and mythology of the Adamites, a unique group believed to have existed during the time of the Garden of Eden. They should not be confused with the sect of early Christian Adamites who were active during the 2nd to 4th centuries CE. Despite sharing the same name, the two groups are entirely unrelated. The Adamites discussed in this article are described in certain interpretations of ancient scriptures as having participated in a union with a rebellious faction of the Elohim known as the Serpent, resulting in a hybrid offspring.</description></item><item><title>Âge d'Or</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/wiki/%C3%A2ge-dor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/wiki/%C3%A2ge-dor/</guid><description>The awaited Golden Age is a concept that refers to a future time of peace, prosperity, and happiness, often viewed as a utopian state in which humanity will live in harmony and fulfillment. The idea of a future Golden Age is found in many spiritual and religious traditions, including astrology, where it is sometimes linked to the arrival of the Age of Aquarius.
In astrology, the Age of Aquarius is an astrological age that is believed to bring about a new era of peace, enlightenment, and spiritual awakening.</description></item><item><title>Alliance noachique</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/wiki/alliance-noachique/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/wiki/alliance-noachique/</guid><description>Etymology # Covenant is not a common term in the English language. The word &amp;ldquo;covenant&amp;rdquo; came into Middle English as covenaunt from the Old French covenant, meaning agreement. This Old French term itself came from the Latin conveniens, which was the present participle of the verb convenio. The Latin verb convenio is made up of two parts: con- meaning together and -venio meaning to come. So, convenio means to come together or to agree.</description></item><item><title>Anciens Bâtisseurs</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/wiki/anciens-b%C3%A2tisseurs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/wiki/anciens-b%C3%A2tisseurs/</guid><description>Ancient Builders typically refers to the architects, engineers, and skilled workers who created structures, such as buildings, temples, pyramids, and other monumental structures, in ancient civilizations. These ancient builders used a variety of materials and techniques, depending on the resources and technological abilities available to them. They often incorporated elements of sacred geometry, religious beliefs, and cultural symbols into their structures, which were sometimes used for religious or political purposes.</description></item><item><title>Antédiluvien</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/wiki/ant%C3%A9diluvien/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/wiki/ant%C3%A9diluvien/</guid><description>Antediluvian refers to a time before the Biblical Great Flood. The exact appearance of the antediluvian world is not described in detail in the Bible or any other historical record. Some religious texts suggest that the antediluvian world was a time of great prosperity, peace, and advanced civilization. However, this colloquially considered largely a matter of speculation and interpretation.
In Raëlism 🔯 # According to the Book Which Tells The Truth, Second Chapter Truth, The Flood, Yahweh says the following about the antediluvian world and its advanced human civilization:</description></item><item><title>Apocalypse</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/wiki/apocalypse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/wiki/apocalypse/</guid><description>The Apocalypse, as described in the biblical Book of Revelation, is a series of events that marks the end of the world as it is known. According to the text, the Apocalypse involves a series of cataclysmic events, including wars, plagues, natural disasters, and the rise of the Antichrist. At the climax of these events, there will be a final battle between good and evil, and Jesus Christ will return to Earth to defeat Satan and establish a new heaven and a new earth.</description></item><item><title>Arbre de la connaissance du bien et du mal</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/wiki/arbre-de-la-connaissance-du-bien-et-du-mal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/wiki/arbre-de-la-connaissance-du-bien-et-du-mal/</guid><description>The Tree of the Knowledge of Good and Evil is a tree mentioned in the book of Genesis in the Bible. According to the biblical story, the Tree of the Knowledge of Good and Evil was a tree in the Garden of Eden that God commanded Adam and Eve not to eat from. However, the serpent tempted Eve to eat from the tree, and she in turn convinced Adam to do the same.</description></item><item><title>Arbre de la Vie</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/wiki/arbre-de-la-vie/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/fr/wiki/arbre-de-la-vie/</guid><description>The Tree of Life is a concept that appears in many cultures and religious traditions, and is often associated with various symbolic and spiritual meanings.
In the Bible, the Tree of Life is mentioned in the book of Genesis, where it is described as a tree that grew in the Garden of Eden and provided immortality to those who ate from its fruit. After Adam and Eve ate from the Tree of Knowledge and were expelled from the Garden, they were prevented from eating from the Tree of Life, thus becoming mortal.</description></item></channel></rss>