<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>archaeoastronomy on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/topics/archaeoastronomy/</link><description>Recent content in archaeoastronomy on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/topics/archaeoastronomy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fingerprints of the Gods: The Evidence of Earth's Lost Civilization</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/fingerprints-of-the-gods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/fingerprints-of-the-gods/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Fingerprints of the Gods: The Evidence of Earth&amp;rsquo;s Lost Civilization&amp;rdquo; by Graham Hancock, published in 1995, explores the hypothesis of a highly advanced civilization existing in prehistory, serving as the progenitor of all known ancient civilizations. Hancock proposes that this civilization, centered around Antarctica, ended catastrophically at the end of the last ice age but passed on significant knowledge in astronomy, architecture, and mathematics. The evidence for this lost civilization, according to Hancock, is found in ancient Egypt and American civilizations like the Olmec, Aztec, and Maya.</description></item><item><title>Hamlet's Mill: An Essay Investigating the Origins of Human Knowledge and Its Transmission Through Myth</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/hamlets-mill/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/resources/hamlets-mill/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Hamlet&amp;rsquo;s Mill: An Essay Investigating the Origins of Human Knowledge and Its Transmission Through Myth,&amp;rdquo; written by Giorgio de Santillana and Hertha von Dechend, presents the argument that ancient mythologies contain sophisticated knowledge of the precession of the equinoxes. This knowledge, they argue, indicates a Neolithic discovery and a long-lived Megalithic civilization of remarkable sophistication, particularly in astronomical observation. The authors suggest that this civilization&amp;rsquo;s knowledge was encoded in myths, often represented by a millstone and a young protagonist, which they interpret primarily through the lens of archaeoastronomy.</description></item></channel></rss>