<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>elohim on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/tags/elohim/</link><description>Recent content in elohim on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/tags/elohim/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Roadmap after first year since launch</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/articles/roadmap-after-first-year-since-launch/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/articles/roadmap-after-first-year-since-launch/</guid><description>👉 Disclaimer: This is a English-only article. The inception of this website traces back to last year&amp;rsquo;s autumn equinox. I was perched in a rooftop bar in Jerusalem, with the Old City stretching out before me in the east. From that moment to now, the content has burgeoned remarkably. I&amp;rsquo;ve dedicated considerable effort to refining the user experience of the site, and the wiki has been meticulously curated, almost to the limits of what a single maintainer can achieve.</description></item><item><title>Let's Lexicon: Elohimite vs. Elohimian</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/articles/lets-lexicon-elohimite-vs.-elohimian/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/articles/lets-lexicon-elohimite-vs.-elohimian/</guid><description>👉 Disclaimer: This is a English-only article. Translating the premises of this article into languages with different ethnolinguistic characteristics. In the broad tapestry of ancient astronaut narratives, from the works of Jean Sendy and Zechariah Sitchin, through to the modern trend of interpreting biblical scriptures literally, as undertaken by scholars such as Mauro Biglino and Paul Anthony Wallis, a unique perspective emerges. On our website, Wheel of Heaven, we delve into one such perspective by contextualizing a new religious movement known as Raëlism, where the term &amp;lsquo;Elohim&amp;rsquo; assumes a pivotal role.</description></item></channel></rss>