<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Esoterica on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/topics/esoterica/</link><description>Recent content in Esoterica on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/topics/esoterica/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Internet Sacred Text Archive</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/internet-sacred-text-archive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/internet-sacred-text-archive/</guid><description>The Internet Sacred Text Archive (ISTA), founded by John Bruno Hare in 1999 in Santa Cruz, California, is a website dedicated to preserving electronic public domain religious texts. Hare, a software engineer, initiated this project from his home as an intellectual challenge, digitizing over 1,000 public domain books on religion, folklore, and mythology to promote religious tolerance through knowledge. The archive&amp;rsquo;s texts are divided into 77 categories, and its maintenance costs are supported by sales of the website&amp;rsquo;s content on DVDs, CDs, or USB flash drives.</description></item><item><title>Kosmographia — The Official Randall Carlson Podcast</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/kosmographia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/kosmographia/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Kosmographia — The Official Randall Carlson Podcast&amp;rdquo; is a thought-provoking and in-depth podcast series hosted by Randall Carlson, a renowned geological and architectural theorist, teacher, and scholar. The podcast delves into a wide array of subjects that intersect science, mythology, geology, and ancient history, reflecting Carlson&amp;rsquo;s multifaceted interests and expertise.
Carlson, known for his meticulous research and comprehensive knowledge, explores theories and evidence related to Earth&amp;rsquo;s geological history, catastrophic events, and the mysteries of ancient civilizations.</description></item></channel></rss>