<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Enzyklopädie on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/wiki/encyclopedia/</link><description>Recent content in Enzyklopädie on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/wiki/encyclopedia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Abraham</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/wiki/abraham/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/wiki/abraham/</guid><description>Abraham is a central figure in Judaism, Christianity, and Islam and is considered the father of these three monotheistic religions. In the Bible, he is described as the father of Isaac and a patriarch of the Israelites. In the Tanakh, he is considered the first Hebrew and the founder of the Jewish nation. In the Quran, Abraham is considered a prophet of Allah and a friend of God.
In the Bible, Abraham is described as:</description></item><item><title>Adam und Eva</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/wiki/adam-und-eva/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/wiki/adam-und-eva/</guid><description>Adam and Eve are the first man and woman according to the creation story in the Bible&amp;rsquo;s book of Genesis. They are considered the first human beings created by God, and are believed to have lived in the Garden of Eden before disobeying God&amp;rsquo;s command and being expelled from the garden (Genesis 3). Adam is described as the first man created by God from the dust of the ground, while Eve is described as the first woman, created from one of Adam&amp;rsquo;s ribs (Genesis 2:7, 2:22).</description></item><item><title>Adamiten</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/wiki/adamiten/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/wiki/adamiten/</guid><description>This article explores the history and mythology of the Adamites, a unique group believed to have existed during the time of the Garden of Eden. They should not be confused with the sect of early Christian Adamites who were active during the 2nd to 4th centuries CE. Despite sharing the same name, the two groups are entirely unrelated. The Adamites discussed in this article are described in certain interpretations of ancient scriptures as having participated in a union with a rebellious faction of the Elohim known as the Serpent, resulting in a hybrid offspring.</description></item><item><title>Adamitischer Existenzkampf</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/wiki/adamitischer-existenzkampf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/wiki/adamitischer-existenzkampf/</guid><description>Sequence of events # The Adamite Struggle refers an to epoch-spanning struggle that started in the Age of Leo, which delineates the course of humanity&amp;rsquo;s evolution from their creation to their eventual emergence as independent and autonomous entities. This narrative presents the perspective of the human Adamites, who were embroiled in a complex political struggle against their creators, the Elohim.
The Adamites, also referred to as early human beings in Eden, were created by Elohimite scientists on Earth.</description></item><item><title>Ancient Astronauts-Hypothese</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/wiki/ancient-astronauts-hypothese/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/wiki/ancient-astronauts-hypothese/</guid><description>The Ancient Astronaut Hypothesis proposes that in ancient times, extraterrestrial beings visited Earth and interacted with humans. Proponents of the theory suggest that evidence of these interactions can be seen in ancient art, legends, and architecture, which they claim cannot be fully explained by conventional historical and scientific explanations. They also argue that certain technological and cultural advancements in human history, such as the building of the pyramids in Egypt or the creation of the Nazca lines in Peru, could not have been achieved without outside influence.</description></item><item><title>Antediluvianisch</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/wiki/antediluvianisch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/wiki/antediluvianisch/</guid><description>Antediluvian refers to a time before the Biblical Great Flood. The exact appearance of the antediluvian world is not described in detail in the Bible or any other historical record. Some religious texts suggest that the antediluvian world was a time of great prosperity, peace, and advanced civilization. However, this colloquially considered largely a matter of speculation and interpretation.
In Raëlism 🔯 # According to the Book Which Tells The Truth, Second Chapter Truth, The Flood, Yahweh says the following about the antediluvian world and its advanced human civilization:</description></item><item><title>Antike Baumeister</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/wiki/antike-baumeister/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/wiki/antike-baumeister/</guid><description>Ancient Builders typically refers to the architects, engineers, and skilled workers who created structures, such as buildings, temples, pyramids, and other monumental structures, in ancient civilizations. These ancient builders used a variety of materials and techniques, depending on the resources and technological abilities available to them. They often incorporated elements of sacred geometry, religious beliefs, and cultural symbols into their structures, which were sometimes used for religious or political purposes.</description></item><item><title>Apokalypse</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/wiki/apokalypse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/wiki/apokalypse/</guid><description>The Apocalypse, as described in the biblical Book of Revelation, is a series of events that marks the end of the world as it is known. According to the text, the Apocalypse involves a series of cataclysmic events, including wars, plagues, natural disasters, and the rise of the Antichrist. At the climax of these events, there will be a final battle between good and evil, and Jesus Christ will return to Earth to defeat Satan and establish a new heaven and a new earth.</description></item><item><title>Archäoastronomie</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/wiki/arch%C3%A4oastronomie/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/wiki/arch%C3%A4oastronomie/</guid><description>Archaeoastronomy is an interdisciplinary field of study that explores the knowledge, practices, and beliefs related to celestial bodies and phenomena in ancient cultures. It combines principles from archaeology, anthropology, and astronomy to analyze and interpret the astronomical significance of archaeological sites, artifacts, and cultural practices. By investigating the ways in which ancient civilizations observed, recorded, and utilized astronomical information, archaeoastronomy aims to enrich our understanding of their worldviews, religious beliefs, and social organization.</description></item><item><title>Arche Noah</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/wiki/arche-noah/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/de/wiki/arche-noah/</guid><description>The story of Noah&amp;rsquo;s Ark is a well-known biblical account from the book of Genesis in the Old Testament. According to the story, God saw that the world had become corrupt and wicked, and decided to cleanse it with a great flood. He chose Noah, a righteous man, to build an ark and gather two of every kind of animal and bird, as well as his family, to survive the flood.</description></item></channel></rss>