<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Articles on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/articles/</link><description>Recent content in Articles on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Roadmap after first year since launch</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/articles/roadmap-after-first-year-since-launch/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/articles/roadmap-after-first-year-since-launch/</guid><description>👉 Disclaimer: This is a English-only article. The inception of this website traces back to last year&amp;rsquo;s autumn equinox. I was perched in a rooftop bar in Jerusalem, with the Old City stretching out before me in the east. From that moment to now, the content has burgeoned remarkably. I&amp;rsquo;ve dedicated considerable effort to refining the user experience of the site, and the wiki has been meticulously curated, almost to the limits of what a single maintainer can achieve.</description></item><item><title>The Great Year and Its Twelve Houses</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/articles/the-great-year-and-its-twelve-houses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/articles/the-great-year-and-its-twelve-houses/</guid><description>👉 Disclaimer: This is a revisited and slightly reworked article taken from an unmaintained blog of Zara Zinsfuss, a main contributor of Wheel of Heaven. The original blog article can still be visited on his Gitlab Pages website: The Great Year and Its Twelve Houses | zara◇zinsfuss The Great Year # Whenever we want to understand our place in the universe, we gaze into the deep night sky, losing ourselves in the myriad of stars within our sight.</description></item><item><title>Let's Lexicon: Elohimite vs. Elohimian</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/articles/lets-lexicon-elohimite-vs.-elohimian/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/articles/lets-lexicon-elohimite-vs.-elohimian/</guid><description>👉 Disclaimer: This is a English-only article. Translating the premises of this article into languages with different ethnolinguistic characteristics. In the broad tapestry of ancient astronaut narratives, from the works of Jean Sendy and Zechariah Sitchin, through to the modern trend of interpreting biblical scriptures literally, as undertaken by scholars such as Mauro Biglino and Paul Anthony Wallis, a unique perspective emerges. On our website, Wheel of Heaven, we delve into one such perspective by contextualizing a new religious movement known as Raëlism, where the term &amp;lsquo;Elohim&amp;rsquo; assumes a pivotal role.</description></item><item><title>Content log 03/23 🪵</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/articles/content-log-03/23/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/articles/content-log-03/23/</guid><description>It has been six months since we launched the Wheel of Heaven Knowledge Base website, and it has been a lot of work ever since. As the primary content creator for the site, I thought it would be helpful to start a content log to recapitulate what has happened and what I have been working on during this time.
In terms of website traffic, we have seen a steady increase since the launch, but the web site has been mostly off the radar for many as of yet.</description></item><item><title>Fact check: Ye did showcase a Raëlian symbol</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/articles/fact-check-ye-did-showcase-a-ra%C3%ABlian-symbol/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/articles/fact-check-ye-did-showcase-a-ra%C3%ABlian-symbol/</guid><description>Ye recently posted a tweet that got him banned (again) from Twitter. Superifically, it looks a lot like some sort of provocation, that is tweeting a picture featuring what appears to be combining two seemingly opposing symbols. Two symbols that carry heavy historical connotations. &amp;ldquo;Love everyone. #lovespeech&amp;rdquo; wrote Ye alongside his provoking tweet. What one may not know however (and what Ye himself may have not known either) is that this intertwined synthetization of two ostensibly unrelated, opposing symbols was not a new creation by Ye or someone affiliated.</description></item><item><title>Hello World! 👋</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/articles/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/articles/hello-world/</guid><description>Hello World! Wheel of Heaven has been launched offically! Wheel of Heaven is a knowledge base exploring the working hypothesis that life on Earth was intelligently designed by an extraterrestrial civilization, the so-called Elohim.
While the working hypothesis is not necessarily something new and there are a certain number of forethinkers within the realm of ancient astronauts, creationism and/or an neo-euhemeristic reading of ancient mythology, the foundation upon which the premises are residing is an unapologetic re-interpretation Raëlism, a new religious movement that goes back to a Frenchman that avowedly met the representative of an extraterrestrial civilization, Yahweh, that left us with an important message of very deep philsophical implications if proven true.</description></item></channel></rss>