<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>documentary-film on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/medium/documentary-film/</link><description>Recent content in documentary-film on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/medium/documentary-film/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ancient Apocalypse</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/ancient-apocalypse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/ancient-apocalypse/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Ancient Apocalypse,&amp;rdquo; a 2022 Netflix documentary series hosted by British writer Graham Hancock, presents a series of pseudoarchaeological theories about an advanced civilization that existed during the last ice age. The series, produced by ITN Productions and highly watched upon release, suggests that this civilization was destroyed in a cataclysm and its survivors introduced agriculture, monumental architecture, and astronomy to hunter-gatherers around the world. Hancock contends that various ancient monuments are evidence of this civilization and accuses archaeologists of ignoring or covering up this alleged evidence.</description></item><item><title>Is Genesis History?</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/is-genesis-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/is-genesis-history/</guid><description>Is Genesis History?&amp;quot; is a 2017 American film directed by Thomas Purifoy Jr., which presents the perspective of Young Earth creationism. This form of creation science challenges established scientific facts regarding the origins of the universe, Earth, solar system, and life itself, advocating for a literal interpretation of the biblical narratives. The film posits that the Earth was created in six 24-hour days and supports the Genesis accounts of Adam and Eve, the fall, a global flood, and the Tower of Babel.</description></item><item><title>The Revelation of the Pyramids</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/the-revelation-of-the-pyramid/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/the-revelation-of-the-pyramid/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The Revelation of the Pyramids,&amp;rdquo; a French documentary directed by Patrice Pooyard and released in 2010, delves into pseudo-historical theories proposed by Jacques Grimault. Grimault&amp;rsquo;s unpublished works suggest a slow cycle of geological changes on Earth, including shifts in magnetic poles, causing catastrophic events every 26,000 years. He theorizes that an ancient civilization, predating ours, was destroyed by these catastrophes, and that they built the Pyramids of Giza and other ancient structures.</description></item><item><title>The Sacred City</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/the-sacred-city/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/ru/resources/the-sacred-city/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;The Sacred City&amp;rdquo; is a documentary film by Dan Gibson that presents a provocative and alternative perspective on the early history of Islam and its sacred geography. Gibson, a historical researcher, embarks on a quest to investigate the origins of Islam, challenging the conventional narrative about the birthplace of the religion.
The central thesis of Gibson&amp;rsquo;s documentary is the controversial claim that the Islamic holy city of Mecca, as known today, was not the original location mentioned in early Islamic texts.</description></item></channel></rss>