<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>See more on</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/intro/see-more/</link><description>Recent content in See more on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.wheelofheaven.io/intro/see-more/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/intro/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/intro/faq/</guid><description>Welcome to the FAQ (Frequently Asked Questions) section of Wheel of Heaven! Here, we provide answers to common questions about our hypothesis, resources, and the broader implications of our research. If you have more questions, feel free to reach out to us.
Table of Contents # What is Wheel of Heaven? The hypothesis Resources and navigation The Great Year and World Ages Attributed to the Elohim Future implications What is Wheel of Heaven?</description></item><item><title>Knowledge base</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/intro/knowledge-base/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/intro/knowledge-base/</guid><description>You made it through the Introduction, but the inquisitive journey doesn&amp;rsquo;t end here. Make sure to check out the Wiki, the Resources and the Blog section of Wheel of Heaven to dive more into the big narrative put forward here.
An informative wiki section filled with entries and points of interest 🔗 A resource area that features web books handpicked by our team 🔗 A frequently updated blog where fresh perspectives and insights are shared 🔗</description></item><item><title>Community</title><link>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/intro/community/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.wheelofheaven.io/intro/community/</guid><description>If the premises of Wheel of Heaven made you more curious, you can also participate on making the experience more worthwhile by helping us out to add missing pieces of information or to translate unavailable content into one of the supported languages.
You can also connect with us through Telegram, Github and/or Twitter. In the header, you&amp;rsquo;re going to find the links to each of these platforms by simply clicking on the corresponding icon.</description></item></channel></rss>